<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<episodes>
  <episode title='Simpsons Roasting on an Open Fire' episode='1' season='1' aired='17 December 1989'>
     Christmas seems doomed for the Simpson family when Homer receives no
    Christmas Bonus. Homer becomes a mall Santa Claus, hoping to make money and
    bring Marge, Bart, Lisa, and baby Maggie, a happy holiday.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart the Genius' episode='2' season='1' aired='14 January 1990'>
     Bart ends up at a school for gifted children after cheating on an IQ test.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer&apos;s Odyssey' episode='3' season='1' aired='21 January 1990'>
     While Bart&apos;s class is touring the Springfield Nuclear Power Plant for
    a field trip, Homer crashes his golf cart into a radioactive pipe. In the
    aftermath, the plant is forced to shutdown and Homer loses his job.
  </episode>
  <episode title='There&apos;s No Disgrace Like Home' episode='4' season='1' aired='28 January 1990'>
     At a company picnic Homer realizes his family is dysfunctional and takes
    them all to therapy where they end up having shock treatment. They are still
    as bad as ever so Homer gets double his money back from Dr Marvin Monroe and
    the Simpsons buy themselves a new TV.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart the General' episode='5' season='1' aired='4 February 1990'>
     School bully Nelson Muntz has been terrorizing his classmates, particularly
    Bart. Bart and one of Nelson&apos;s goons get into a fight at school (when
    Bart was sticking up for Lisa), and in the aftermath Nelson accidentally
    gets a bloody nose. Nelson makes good on his threats to beat up Bart. Bart
    winds up having nightmares about Nelson stalking him, and later envisions
    his funeral. Finally, Grampa takes Bart to Herman, a Vietnam veteran who has
    had one of his arms amputated, to plan a strategy for getting back at
    Nelson. Bart commissions all his schoolmates whom Nelson has bullied and -
    in a classic parody of war movies such as Patton - trains them for their
    revenge. One afternoon after school, Bart and his army enact their
    operative, pelting Nelson and his goons with water balloons until he
    surrenders. The revenge is successful, and Bart and Nelson begin a grudging
    friendship.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Moaning Lisa' episode='6' season='1' aired='11 February 1990'>
     A depressed Lisa&apos;s spirit is lifted when she meets a jazz-man,
    Bleeding Gums Murphy.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Call of the Simpsons' episode='7' season='1' aired='18 February 1990'>
     Ned Flanders shows off his newly purchased (and monstrous) motor home to
    the Simpsons. In a fit of oneupmanship, Homer decides he needs one too.
    Homer&apos;s credit is very poor, but he wants that motor home, so he buys
    one whose oil is leaking and appears to be held together by chicken wire and
    duct tape. With their new motor home, Homer takes the family on an outing in
    the woods. Homer quickly loses his way and everyone bails from the motor
    home just before it tumbles into a large ravine. The family is forced to
    rough it the rest of the way. Maggie becomes separated from the family and
    takes refuge with a family of bears. Meanwhile, Homer and Bart lose their
    clothing and have to wear leaves. Homer quickly falls into a stream and
    becomes covered with mud. A couple staying in the woods, concluding that
    what they&apos;ve seen is Bigfoot, takes a picture of Homer and sends it to
    a TV station. Soon, the woods are crawling with media representatives,
    hoping to get their own glimpse. A park ranger shoots Homer with a
    tranquilizer and he is taken to a laboratory for analysis. However, the
    results - either it&apos;s a below-average human or a brilliant beast, a
    German scientist says - are inconclusive.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Telltale Head' episode='8' season='1' aired='25 February 1990'>
     Bart gets more than he bargained for when he saws the head off a statue of
    the town&apos;s founder.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Life on the Fast Lane' episode='9' season='1' aired='18 March 1990'>
     Marge contemplates an affair with a handsome bowling instructor.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer&apos;s Night Out' episode='10' season='1' aired='25 March 1990'>
     Bart uses his new miniature &quot;spy&quot; camera to take candid pictures
    around the household; meanwhile, Homer is preparing to go to a bachelor
    party for his co-worker at the Springfield Nuclear Power Plant. While at the
    party, Homer is invited to dance on stage with a stripper. Bart (who is
    dining with the rest of the family in the next-door restaurant) uses his
    camera to snap a photo of Homer and the dancer having a great time. At
    school, Martin develops the picture, which - after he compliments
    Bart&apos;s work - gets distributed around school, and eventually around
    town. Marge sees the photo and is outraged. Homer arrives home, where Marge
    immediately confronts her husband and kicks him out of the house.
    Eventually, Marge agrees to let him back in on the condition he take Bart
    around to meet the stripper and show that she is not a sex object. After
    almost winding up on stage at another of the dancer&apos;s performances,
    Homer does as he is asked and all is forgiven.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Crepes of Wrath' episode='11' season='1' aired='15 April 1990'>
     Bart flushes a cherry bomb at school, nearly injuring Principal
    Skinner&apos;s mother, Agnes, in the process. An exasperated Skinner tells
    Homer and Marge that since expulsion would not do Bart any good, he&apos;s
    placing him in a foreign-exchange student program. Bart is sent to France,
    where his host family are unethical winemakers who plan to employ him as a
    slave.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Krusty Gets Busted' episode='12' season='1' aired='29 April 1990'>
     Homer witnesses a robbery at the Kwik-E-Mart convenience store, where the
    culprit is a man dressed like Bart&apos;s hero, Krusty the Clown. Does the
    children&apos;s television host have a sinister second life, or is there
    more to the story than meets the eye?
  </episode>
  <episode title='Some Enchanted Evening' episode='13' season='1' aired='13 May 1990'>
     Homer and Marge enjoy a night out on the town. Meanwhile, at home, the kids
    deal with a diabolical babysitter.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart Gets an F' episode='1' season='2' aired='11 October 1990'>
     Bart&apos;s teacher, Mrs. Krabappel, has become fed up with his
    lackadaisical scholastic habits. After bluffing his way through a book
    report and failing a geography exam, Krabappel gives Bart an ultimatum:
    Shape up or be retained in fourth grade.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Simpson and Delilah' episode='2' season='2' aired='18 October 1990'>
     Homer lies on a medical insurance form to buy a &quot;miracle&quot;
    hair-restoring drug.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror' episode='3' season='2' aired='25 October 1990'>
     In this trilogy of horror-themed Halloween stories, Bart and Lisa attempt
    to scare each other with tales of the macabre. In first,&quot;Bad Dream
    House&quot;, the Simpsons inhabit a haunted home, which possesses their
    souls, and causes them to attempt to kill each other. But after spending
    enough time with the Simpsons, it is the house, which kill itself, vanishing
    into another dimension. In the second segment, &quot;Hungry are the
    Damned&quot;, the Simpsons accuse the monsters of planning to eat them, but
    the offended aliens reveal they were only planning a sumptuous meal for the
    family. In the third segment, a satire of Poe&apos;s &quot;The Raven&quot;,
    a grief-stricken Homer is tormented by bad bird Bart.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Two Cars in Every Garage and Three Eyes on Every Fish' episode='4' season='2' aired='1 November 1990'>
     A three-eyed fish is caught in the Springfield River downstream from the
    nuclear plant, leading to a government safety inspection. When Mr. Burns is
    told that the plant will be shut down, he gets drunk in his car with Homer.
    Homer remarks that if Burns were governor, he could make new laws to keep
    the plant open. Burns seizes on this remark and announces his candidacy.
    Afraid for his job, Homer pushes his family to campaign for Burns, but Marge
    is a staunch supporter of the incumbent, Mary Bailey. On the night before
    the election, Burns dines at the Simpson home as a publicity stunt.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Dancin&apos; Homer' episode='5' season='2' aired='8 November 1990'>
     Homer&apos;s heckling of the Springfield Isotopes baseball team&apos;s
    mascot during one of their games leads to his appointment as the new mascot.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Dead Putting Society' episode='6' season='2' aired='15 November 1990'>
     Overcome with jealousy at Ned Flanders&apos;s affluent lifestyle and
    affectionate family, Homer paints him as a snobbish jerk to the rest of his
    family and looks eagerly for an opportunity to show him up. He finds it in
    an upcoming miniature golf tournament, and enters Bart against Ned&apos;s
    son Todd.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart vs. Thanksgiving' episode='7' season='2' aired='22 November 1990'>
     On Thanksgiving, Bart learns about the meaning of the holiday when he runs
    away from home (after getting into a fight), then shares a turkey dinner
    with homeless people at a soup kitchen.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart the Daredevil' episode='8' season='2' aired='6 December 1990'>
     After seeing a motorcycle daredevil at the monster truck show, Bart becomes
    a death-defying daredevil on his skateboard.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Itchy and Scratchy and Marge' episode='9' season='2' aired='20 December 1990'>
     Marge becomes a crusader against cartoon violence after watching &apos;The
    Itchy and Scratchy Show&apos;.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart Gets Hit by a Car' episode='10' season='2' aired='10 January 1991'>
     While skateboarding down the street, Bart is hit by a car driven by Mr.
    Burns. Homer turns down Mr. Burns&apos; token offer of $100, and instead
    hires ambulance-chaser Lionel Hutz to bring an outrageous lawsuit.
  </episode>
  <episode title='One Fish, Two Fish, Blowfish, Blue Fish' episode='11' season='2' aired='24 January 1991'>
     What would you do if you were told you had only 24 hours to live?
    That&apos;s what this episode explores when Homer is told just that.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Way We Was' episode='12' season='2' aired='31 January 1991'>
     Homer and Marge tell the story of how they met and fell in love in high
    school.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer vs. Lisa and the Eighth Commandment' episode='13' season='2' aired='7 February 1991'>
     Homer gets a crooked cable guy to install free cable in the Simpson home.
    Lisa faces an ethical crises over her family&apos;s stealing.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Principal Charming' episode='14' season='2' aired='14 February 1991'>
     After attending a co-worker&apos;s wedding, a depressed Selma begs Marge to
    help her find a man. Marge sets Homer to the task, and Homer is impressed by
    Principal Skinner. Homer invites Skinner to the Simpson home for dinner, but
    accidentally introduces him to Selma&apos;s twin, Patty.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Oh Brother, Where Art Thou?' episode='15' season='2' aired='21 February 1991'>
     Homer&apos;s new design ruins his half-brother&apos;s car empire.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart&apos;s Dog Gets an F' episode='16' season='2' aired='7 March 1991'>
     After an uncontrollable Santa&apos;s Little Helper destroys several
    important Simpson possessions, Homer announces that he will be thrown out of
    the house unless he completes obedience training.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Old Money' episode='17' season='2' aired='28 March 1991'>
     After Grandpa Simpson&apos;s new girlfriend leaves him $106,000 in her
    will, he tries to decide what to do with it.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Brush with Greatness' episode='18' season='2' aired='11 April 1991'>
     Homer goes on a diet and Marge enrolls in an art class.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lisa&apos;s Substitute' episode='19' season='2' aired='25 April 1991'>
     Lisa has a crush on her substitute teacher, who seemingly represents
    everything that Homer is not. Meanwhile, Bart decides to run for class
    president, and becomes the overwhelming favorite.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The War of the Simpsons' episode='20' season='2' aired='2 May 1991'>
     Homer can&apos;t decide which is more important: going through a counseling
    seminar to save his marriage, or skipping out to catch a legendary fish.
    Back at home, Bart and Lisa try to take advantage of Grandpa, who is their
    babysitter.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Three Men and a Comic Book' episode='21' season='2' aired='9 May 1991'>
     Bart, Milhouse and Martin each pitch in to buy an expensive comic book,
    which has disastrous results on their friendship.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Blood Feud' episode='22' season='2' aired='11 August 1991'>
     Bart saves Mr. Burns&apos;s life. But Homer becomes enraged when Mr. Burns
    doesn&apos;t return the favor by sending the Simpsons what he considers to
    be an appropriate &quot;thank you&quot; gift.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Stark Raving Dad' episode='1' season='3' aired='19 September 1991'>
     Homer accidentally lands in a mental hospital and ends up sharing a cage
    with a white man who thinks he&apos;s Michael Jackson.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Mr. Lisa Goes to Washington' episode='2' season='3' aired='26 September 1991'>
     Lisa enters a contest and wins a trip to Washington DC for the whole
    family. While there she discovers corruption and decides to expose the
    corrupt official.
  </episode>
  <episode title='When Flanders Failed' episode='3' season='3' aired='3 October 1991'>
     Ned Flanders opens a mall store catering to lefties. Homer, however, wishes
    Flanders would fail.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart the Murderer' episode='4' season='3' aired='10 October 1991'>
     Bart stumbles upon the local mafia boss, and starts working for him on the
    side. When Principal Skinner goes missing after punishing Bart, he and Fat
    Tony&apos;s gang are suspected of killing him, but they try to get Bart to
    take the rap.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer Defined' episode='5' season='3' aired='17 October 1991'>
     Homer is a hero after averting a nuclear meltdown that he nearly caused,
    but he doesn&apos;t want to tell anyone that he stopped it completely by
    accident.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Like Father, Like Clown' episode='6' season='3' aired='24 October 1991'>
     When the Simpsons have Krusty the Clown over for dinner, he says grace in
    Hebrew, and recalls his difficult relationship with his father, a rabbi.
    Bart and Lisa try to reunite the two of them.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror II' episode='7' season='3' aired='31 October 1991'>
     The Simpson family receives a severed monkey&apos;s paw which can grant
    wishes, Bart gains magical powers which he uses to turn Homer into a
    Jack-in-the-box, and Mr. Burns uses Homer&apos;s brain to create a robot.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lisa&apos;s Pony' episode='8' season='3' aired='7 November 1991'>
     After ruining Lisa&apos;s performance at the school talent show, Homer
    tries to make it up by buying her a pony.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Saturdays of Thunder' episode='9' season='3' aired='14 November 1991'>
     After Homer fails a fathering test, he decides to help Bart build his Soap
    Box Derby racer. But Bart dumps Homer and their racer after Martin&apos;s
    far superior vehicle suddenly becomes available.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Flaming Moe&apos;s' episode='10' season='3' aired='21 November 1991'>
     Moe claims that a drink that Homer invented is his own. After the drink
    makes the bar a local hot spot, Moe gains a number of fair-weather friends
    but loses Homer&apos;s friendship.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Burns Verkaufen der Kraftwerk' episode='11' season='3' aired='5 December 1991'>
     Burns decides to retire and sells the power plant to a German consortium
    for an exorbitant price. Homer&apos;s laziness and inefficiency are quickly
    exposed by his new bosses, and he is laid off.
  </episode>
  <episode title='I Married Marge' episode='12' season='3' aired='26 December 1991'>
     As Marge goes to the doctor for a pregnancy test, Homer tells the children
    of the events leading up to his marriage and Bart&apos;s birth.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Radio Bart' episode='13' season='3' aired='9 January 1992'>
     After Bart receives a microphone which can transmit through radios, he
    decides to pull a series of pranks, and eventually convinces the town that a
    boy has fallen down a well.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lisa the Greek' episode='14' season='3' aired='23 January 1992'>
     Homer uses Lisa (and her prognostic skills) to help him bet on football
    games.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer Alone' episode='15' season='3' aired='6 February 1992'>
     While Marge spends a couple of days at Rancho Relaxo after she has a
    breakdown, Bart and Lisa stay with Patty and Selma, and Homer stays at home
    to take care of Maggie.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart the Lover' episode='16' season='3' aired='13 February 1992'>
     After Ms. Krabappel gives Bart a month of detention, Bart gets his revenge
    on her by responding to her newspaper singles ad. Homer begins a &quot;swear
    jar&quot; to keep him cursing.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer at the Bat' episode='17' season='3' aired='20 February 1992'>
     Homer and his co-workers qualify the plant&apos;s softball team for the
    league final, but Mr. Burns hires 9 professional MLB players to win a $1
    million bet.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Separate Vocations' episode='18' season='3' aired='27 February 1992'>
     The results of a standardized test steer Bart in the direction of law and
    order at Springfield Elementary School. However, Lisa becomes so depressed
    by her results that she turns to juvenile delinquency.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Dog of Death' episode='19' season='3' aired='12 March 1992'>
     The Simpsons wind up regretting paying for an expensive surgery for
    Santa&apos;s Little Helper. He then runs away from home, winds up in the
    animal shelter, and is adopted by Mr. Burns to become an attack dog.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Colonel Homer' episode='20' season='3' aired='26 March 1992'>
     Homer becomes the manager of a beautiful young country singer, and finds
    himself almost attracted to her, sparking Marge&apos;s jealousy.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Black Widower' episode='21' season='3' aired='9 April 1992'>
     Sideshow Bob gets out of jail and plots to take his revenge on Bart by
    marrying his Aunt Selma and killing her.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Otto Show' episode='22' season='3' aired='23 April 1992'>
     After Otto loses his job as a school bus driver because he doesn&apos;t
    have a license, Bart talks Homer and Marge into having Otto stay with them
    until he gets back on his feet.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart&apos;s Friend Falls in Love' episode='23' season='3' aired='7 May 1992'>
     Milhouse falls in love with Samantha, a new transfer student, and Bart
    becomes jealous of all the time they are spending together. Homer orders a
    subliminal weight loss tape, but is given a vocabulary builder by mistake.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Brother, Can You Spare Two Dimes?' episode='24' season='3' aired='27 August 1992'>
     After Homer &quot;wins&quot; a $2000 settlement with the plant for
    radiation affecting his sperm count, his brother Herb comes to Springfield
    with an idea that could help him get his fortune back.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Kamp Krusty' episode='1' season='4' aired='24 September 1992'>
     Bart and Lisa go off for the summer to Krusty&apos;s camp for kids, but
    instead of meeting Krusty they meet his bean-counting surrogate, Mr. Black.
    With their children gone, Homer and Marge enjoy a romantic summer, but Bart
    and Lisa are put to work making crummy merchandise, until Krusty returns and
    sets things right-by taking the kids to Tijuana.
  </episode>
  <episode title='A Streetcar Named Marge' episode='2' season='4' aired='1 October 1992'>
     Marge wins the lead in a musical production of &quot;A Streetcar Named
    Desire&quot;, in which Ned Flanders plays Stanley Kowalski. Marge is
    infuriated by Homer&apos;s brutishness and insensitivity during
    preproduction, until he sees the play and reveals to Marge that he has
    grasped its meaning. While rehearsing, Marge sticks Maggie in the Ayn Rand
    Day Care Center, where her pacifier is immediately taken from her, and a la
    &quot;The Great Escape&quot;, she must struggle to win it back.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer the Heretic' episode='3' season='4' aired='8 October 1992'>
     Homer decides not to attend church one Sunday and has the time of his life
    and vows never to return to church again, however one Sunday after falling
    asleep while smoking a cigar he accidentally sets fire to The Simpsons
    house, Flanders spots the flames and rescues him, Homer comes to his senses
    and turns up at church the following Sunday(asleep).
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lisa the Beauty Queen' episode='4' season='4' aired='15 October 1992'>
     With her self-esteem shattered by a school carnival cartoonist, Homer
    decides to enter Lisa in a local children&apos;s beauty contest, which she
    ends up winning by default. But when she finds out how heavily involved
    Laramie Tobacco is in using the contest to sell cigarettes, she uses her
    position as a platform against the tobacco industry and other establishments
    of power and corruption.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror III' episode='5' season='4' aired='29 October 1992'>
     In &quot;Clown Without Pity&quot;, a Krusty the Clown doll goes berserk in
    the Simpson home. In &quot;King Homer&quot;, Marge is wooed by a giant ape.
    And final story, In &quot;Dial &apos;Z&apos; for Zombies&quot;, Bart&apos;s
    attempt to bring back the family cat turns the town of Springfield into a
    pack of bloodthirsty zombies.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Itchy &amp; Scratchy: The Movie' episode='6' season='4' aired='3 November 1992'>
     Pulling one prank too many costs Bart the opportunity to see the Itchy and
    Scratchy Movie.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Marge Gets a Job' episode='7' season='4' aired='5 November 1992'>
     Marge takes a job at the nuclear plant to help pay for the house&apos;s
    foundation repair, and Burns becomes smitten by her.
  </episode>
  <episode title='New Kid on the Block' episode='8' season='4' aired='12 November 1992'>
     Bart finds himself attracted to the 15-year-old new neighbor, Laura. Homer
    sues an All-You-Can-Eat buffet.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Mr. Plow' episode='9' season='4' aired='19 November 1992'>
     Homer buys a truck with an attached snow plow after he destroys his car,
    and to pay for it, he starts a snow shoveling business, calling himself Mr.
    Plow. It all goes off without a hitch, until he finds himself in competition
    with The Plow King, a.k.a. Barney Gumbel. Now begins the winter of
    discontent.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lisa&apos;s First Word' episode='10' season='4' aired='3 December 1992'>
     While trying to coax Maggie into saying her first word, Homer &amp; Marge
    talk about how Lisa spoke hers.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer&apos;s Triple Bypass' episode='11' season='4' aired='17 December 1992'>
     Years of poor eating habits catch up with Homer when he suffers a massive
    heart attack. The family can&apos;t afford the triple bypass operation he
    needs from Dr. Hibbert, so they go to a discount quack named Nick Riviera.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Marge vs. the Monorail' episode='12' season='4' aired='14 January 1993'>
     After receiving a considerable donation of money, the people of Springfield
    decide what to spend it on. Enter Lyle Langley, a jocular salesman who gets
    Springfield hooked on a monorail system. After the monorail is up and
    running, and with Homer as the conductor, it&apos;s time for the maiden
    voyage. Little do the people know they have just boarded a one-way train to
    Hell.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Selma&apos;s Choice' episode='13' season='4' aired='21 January 1993'>
     Selma starts to feel broody, but after taking Bart and Lisa to Duff
    Gardens, she changes her mind.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Brother from the Same Planet' episode='14' season='4' aired='4 February 1993'>
     After Homer forgets to pick up Bart from soccer practice, Bart joins a
    mentor program called Big Brothers presenting himself as an orphan, and is
    assigned a big brother called Tom. When Homer finds out, he joins the
    program too as a big brother.
  </episode>
  <episode title='I Love Lisa' episode='15' season='4' aired='11 February 1993'>
     Feeling sorry for Ralph, Lisa sends him a valentine card, having developed
    a crush on her Ralph invites Lisa to go see the Krusty the Clown show, she
    accepts but after Krusty asks them if there boyfriend and girlfriend Lisa
    lets Ralph no that she just wants them to be friends.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Duffless' episode='16' season='4' aired='18 February 1993'>
     After Homer is arrested for DUI, and loses his driver&apos;s license, he is
    put to the ultimate test when Marge pressures him to give up beer for a
    month.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Last Exit to Springfield' episode='17' season='4' aired='11 March 1993'>
     Homer becomes union leader and leads a company strike when Mr. Burns takes
    away the company dental plan.
  </episode>
  <episode title='So It&apos;s Come to This: A Simpsons Clip Show' episode='18' season='4' aired='1 April 1993'>
     Homer plays a series of (childish) practical jokes on Bart. To get even,
    Bart uses a paint mixer at a local hardware store to shake up a can of
    Homer&apos;s beer. Homer opens the can, resulting in a huge explosion that
    seriously injures the Simpsons patriarch.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Front' episode='19' season='4' aired='15 April 1993'>
     Homer goes back to school after it is revealed that he never graduated.
    Meanwhile, Bart and Lisa ghostwrite for Itchy &amp; Scratchy using
    Abe&apos;s name.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Whacking Day' episode='20' season='4' aired='29 April 1993'>
     Marge attempts to home school Bart after he is expelled from Springfield
    Elementary. Meanwhile, Lisa protests a barbaric local holiday centered
    around clubbing snakes to death.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Marge in Chains' episode='21' season='4' aired='6 May 1993'>
     A misunderstanding leads to Marge being imprisoned for shoplifting. In her
    absence, the family and eventually, the town descend into chaos.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Krusty Gets Kancelled' episode='22' season='4' aired='13 May 1993'>
     A massive advertising blitz announces the arrival of something named
    &quot;Gabbo.&quot; Eventually, Gabbo is revealed to be a Howdy Doddy-esque
    dummy, with Arthur Crandall as the ventriloquist.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer&apos;s Barbershop Quartet' episode='1' season='5' aired='30 September 1993'>
     After the kids find a record with Homer&apos;s picture on it, he recalls
    the story of how he achieved fame in the 1980s with his barbershop quartet
    The Be Sharps.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Cape Feare' episode='2' season='5' aired='7 October 1993'>
     An anonymous letter writer makes ominous threats to Bart. The Simpsons
    discover they were sent by Sideshow Bob who, when released from prison,
    harasses the Simpsons and then attempts to kill Bart with a machete. But
    Bob&apos;s vanity foils him yet again.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer Goes to College' episode='3' season='5' aired='14 October 1993'>
     Homer is fired from his position in the power plant as Safety Inspector
    after a regulation inspector discovers he doesn&apos;t have certification
    for it. He goes back to college to get certified for his old job.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Rosebud' episode='4' season='5' aired='21 October 1993'>
     Mr. Burns goes on a desperate quest to recover his cherished childhood toy
    Bobo, a bear which is now in Maggie&apos;s possession.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror IV' episode='5' season='5' aired='28 October 1993'>
     When Homer announces he would sell his soul for a donut, the Devil,
    disguised as Ned Flanders, shows up to take him up on the offer. Second Act,
    while ridings to school, Bart believe he sees a malevolent gremlin on the
    side of the bus. And final act, Mr. Burns is Dracula, in a spoof of Francis
    Ford Coppola&apos;s vampire film.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Marge on the Lam' episode='6' season='5' aired='4 November 1993'>
     A girl&apos;s night out turns into a high speed chase when Marge learns her
    friend is driving a stolen car.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart&apos;s Inner Child' episode='7' season='5' aired='11 November 1993'>
     Brad Goodman, a self-help guru, identifies Bart as a role model for
    personal happiness, because he is in touch with his inner child. Soon the
    entire town begins to behave like Bart.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Boy Scoutz &apos;n the Hood' episode='8' season='5' aired='18 November 1993'>
     Bart wakes up after a sugar bender to find that he has joined the Junior
    Campers. Although he hates the club at first, he eventually grows to enjoy
    it. When a father/son rafting trip is announced, Homer unwittingly strands
    the group at sea.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Last Temptation of Homer' episode='9' season='5' aired='9 December 1993'>
     Homer&apos;s marriage is in trouble when he develops an attraction to a new
    co-worker.
  </episode>
  <episode title='$pringfield (or How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Legalized Gambling)' episode='10' season='5' aired='16 December 1993'>
     Springfield decides to legalize gambling to revitalize its economy. Marge
    develops a gambling problem, while Mr. Burns develops a Howard Hughes
    complex.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer the Vigilante' episode='11' season='5' aired='6 January 1994'>
     An outbreak of burglaries inspires Homer to lead a vigilante group.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart Gets Famous' episode='12' season='5' aired='3 February 1994'>
     Bart becomes an overnight sensation as the &quot;I didn&apos;t do it&quot;
    boy on Krusty&apos;s show.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer and Apu' episode='13' season='5' aired='10 February 1994'>
     Homer participates in a hidden camera investigation of unsanitary food
    preparation at the Kwik-E-Mart, which costs Apu his job. Apu then enlists
    Homer&apos;s help on a journey to India to get his job back, while James
    Woods becomes the new Kwik-E-Mart clerk, as part of his research for a film
    project.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lisa vs. Malibu Stacy' episode='14' season='5' aired='17 February 1994'>
     Lisa leads a protest against a talking doll she perceives as being sexist.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Deep Space Homer' episode='15' season='5' aired='24 February 1994'>
     The powers that be at NASA, distraught over low television ratings for
    their space launches, decide to improve them by putting a private citizen on
    their next space shuttle. After receiving an angry phone call from Homer,
    they decide he is their man.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer Loves Flanders' episode='16' season='5' aired='17 March 1994'>
     After Ned Flanders helps Homer get tickets to an important football game,
    he and Homer become good friends. But Homer takes the friendship too far
    with his stupid antics, oblivious to the fact that Ned is beginning to hate
    him.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart Gets an Elephant' episode='17' season='5' aired='31 March 1994'>
     After winning a phone-in competition Bart has a choice of prize of either
    $10,000 or an elephant, he chooses the latter, naming him Stampy. The
    Simpsons are in chaos after Stampy wrecks the house and eats all the food.
    They have no alternative, Stampy must go to an animal refuge.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Burns&apos; Heir' episode='18' season='5' aired='14 April 1994'>
     After a near-death experience, Burns holds auditions for his heir and after
    Bart smashes his windows he chooses Bart.Bart moves in with Burns but when
    he&apos;s forced to choose between Burns and his family he chooses the
    latter.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Sweet Seymour Skinner&apos;s Baadasssss Song' episode='19' season='5' aired='28 April 1994'>
     Bart takes Santa&apos;s little helper to school with him on inspection day
    and gets Skinner fired, Bart is pleased until Ned Flandres is made his
    replacement.Bart sets out to find Skinner and get him reinstated.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Boy Who Knew Too Much' episode='20' season='5' aired='5 May 1994'>
     After playing hooky from school, Bart sneaks in to Mayor Quimby&apos;s
    nephew Freddy&apos;s birthday party and witnesses a confrontation between
    Freddy and a waiter, Freddy is accused of beating the waiter but Bart knows
    what really happened, should he keep quiet or tell the truth and risk
    getting Cort playing hooky?
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lady Bouvier&apos;s Lover' episode='21' season='5' aired='12 May 1994'>
     Abe falls in love with Marge&apos;s mother, but must compete with Mr. Burns
    for her heart.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Secrets of a Successful Marriage' episode='22' season='5' aired='19 May 1994'>
     Homer is given the task of teaching an adult education class about
    relationships. He fails to woo the class until he starts talking about his
    and Marge&apos;s sex life. When Marge finds out, she orders him not to talk
    about their private life again. But then he invites his entire class to
    dinner. This is the final straw for Marge and she chucks him out of the
    house. He then moves in to Bart&apos;s tree house. After seeing the error of
    his ways he asks Marge for a second chance. She accepts and the two
    reconcile.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart of Darkness' episode='1' season='6' aired='4 September 1994'>
     In a Rear Window parody, the Simpsons buy a swimming pool and everybody in
    the neighborhood joins in the enjoyment--except for Bart, whose broken leg
    prevents him from swimming. He soon becomes obsessed with looking through
    his telescope and even suspects Ned Flanders of murdering his wife.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lisa&apos;s Rival' episode='2' season='6' aired='11 September 1994'>
     Lisa is jealous when a new girl in class is smarter than she is. Meanwhile,
    Homer obtains a massive amount of sugar.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Another Simpsons Clip Show' episode='3' season='6' aired='25 September 1994'>
     The family recalls past tales of lost love.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Itchy &amp; Scratchy Land' episode='4' season='6' aired='2 October 1994'>
     A family vacation to Itchy &amp; Scratchy Land turns disastrous when the
    robots malfunction and turn on the tourists.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Sideshow Bob Roberts' episode='5' season='6' aired='9 October 1994'>
     Sideshow Bob is released from prison, runs for mayor as a Republican, and
    defeats &quot;Diamond&quot; Joe Quimby in the election. But a
    &quot;Deep-Throat&quot;-type informant tells Bart and Lisa that he was
    fraudulently elected. It&apos;s up to them to find the evidence.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror V' episode='6' season='6' aired='30 October 1994'>
     The Simpsons are employed on Mr. Burns&apos;s country estate-and Homer goes
    insane. And act two, Homer&apos;s attempt to repair a toaster lead him
    repeatedly back into the past-and he inadvertently changes the future. And
    the final act, the school cafeteria turn to an unusual source of food-and
    schoolchildren start mysteriously disappearing.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart&apos;s Girlfriend' episode='7' season='6' aired='6 November 1994'>
     Bart falls for Reverend Lovejoy&apos;s daughter and is surprised when she
    becomes a bad influence on him.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lisa on Ice' episode='8' season='6' aired='13 November 1994'>
     Homer gives all his attention to Bart because he is the star of his hockey
    team, which makes Lisa jealous. But when a rival team discovers that she is
    an excellent goalie, Bart suddenly has rival for Homer&apos;s attention.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer Badman' episode='9' season='6' aired='27 November 1994'>
     Homer and Marge hire college co-ed Ashley Grant to baby-sit the kids while
    they go to a candy convention. While driving Ashley home, Homer shows poor
    tact when he attempts to retrieve a piece of Gummy Venus that became stuck
    to the back of Ashley&apos;s pants. Things are blown way out of proportion
    when Ashley interprets Homer&apos;s innocent actions as a sexual advance,
    prompting her to mount a huge anti-harassment campaign against Homer.
    Several attempts to exonerate himself - most notably, a totally inaccurate
    segment on the tabloid TV show &quot;Rock Bottom&quot; - only make things
    worse. As the media coverage intensifies, his friends turn against him and
    his name becomes comedy fodder, Homer becomes resigned to his tarnished
    reputation. Finally, after Lisa produces a segment for a cable-access TV
    show (where Homer defends himself), Groundskeeper Willie finally produces
    evidence to exonerate the Simpson patriarch.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Grampa vs. Sexual Inadequacy' episode='10' season='6' aired='4 December 1994'>
     Homer and Abe hit the road to sell Abe&apos;s miraculous aphrodisiac.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Fear of Flying' episode='11' season='6' aired='18 December 1994'>
     Marge goes into therapy to cure her of her traumatizing fear of flying.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer the Great' episode='12' season='6' aired='8 January 1995'>
     Homer becomes a member of a mysterious organization called the Stonecutters
    and is heralded as &quot;the chosen one.&quot;
  </episode>
  <episode title='And Maggie Makes Three' episode='13' season='6' aired='22 January 1995'>
     Homer recounts the story of Maggie&apos;s birth when the kids ask why there
    are no photos of her in the family album.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart&apos;s Comet' episode='14' season='6' aired='5 February 1995'>
     Bart discovers a comet that is on a collision course with Springfield.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homie the Clown' episode='15' season='6' aired='12 February 1995'>
     Homer becomes a Krusty the Clown stand-in, but is mistaken for the real
    Krusty by the Springfield mafia.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart vs. Australia' episode='16' season='6' aired='19 February 1995'>
     Lisa tells Bart that toilet water swirls in the opposite direction in the
    Southern Hemisphere. Determined to find out if this is true, Bart makes a
    collect call to Australia. When the father of the boy he called finds out
    about the charges, it sparks an international incident. The Simpsons must
    travel to Australia to repair relations with the United States.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer vs. Patty and Selma' episode='17' season='6' aired='26 February 1995'>
     Desperate for money, Homer takes a loan from Patty and Selma. Meanwhile,
    Bart discovers a natural talent for ballet.
  </episode>
  <episode title='A Star Is Burns' episode='18' season='6' aired='5 March 1995'>
     Mr. Burns hosts a film festival in Springfield to improve his image. Film
    critic Jay Sherman, of &quot;The Critic&quot; is invited, and stays with the
    Simpsons.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lisa&apos;s Wedding' episode='19' season='6' aired='19 March 1995'>
     A fortune teller gives Lisa a look at her wedding in the year 2010.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Two Dozen and One Greyhounds' episode='20' season='6' aired='9 April 1995'>
     Santa&apos;s Little Helper has puppies, and Mr. Burns schemes to steal them
    and make them into a coat.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The PTA Disbands' episode='21' season='6' aired='16 April 1995'>
     Marge fills in for Mrs. Krabappel during a teachers&apos; strike.
  </episode>
  <episode title='&apos;Round Springfield' episode='22' season='6' aired='30 April 1995'>
     When Bart swallows a hazardous prize from a cereal box and winds up in the
    hospital, Lisa finds out her jazz idol Bleeding Gums Murphy has a room of
    his own there. Sadly, this turns out to be his deathbed, and not only is she
    upset about him dying, but she realizes that nobody will ever remember him
    for his music, unless she does something about it.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Springfield Connection' episode='23' season='6' aired='7 May 1995'>
     Marge deals with corruption and crime when she joins the Springfield police
    force.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lemon of Troy' episode='24' season='6' aired='14 May 1995'>
     Shelbyville kids hijack Springfield&apos;s sacred lemon tree after being
    pelted with lemons, and Bart leads a guerrilla war against them (I say a
    war, but it&apos;s nowhere near violent.) They find out that the tree is in
    &quot;the impenetrable fortress of suburbia&quot;- a car impound lot, owned
    by the leader&apos;s (Shelby&apos;s) dad. Homer and the parents of the kids
    find them and team up with them to get the tree back. But how are they gonna
    get it from a car impound lot?
  </episode>
  <episode title='Who Shot Mr. Burns?: Part 1' episode='25' season='6' aired='21 May 1995'>
     Mr. Burns steals oil from Springfield Elementary, and one day, he is shot,
    with no indication on who did it.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Who Shot Mr. Burns?: Part 2' episode='1' season='7' aired='17 September 1995'>
     In the conclusion of the first part that ended season six, we are revealed
    in the first episode of season seven who actually shot Mr. Burns.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Radioactive Man' episode='2' season='7' aired='24 September 1995'>
     Milhouse is cast as Radioactive Man&apos;s sidekick in a Hollywood
    production of the comic book.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Home Sweet Home-Diddily-Dum-Doodily' episode='3' season='7' aired='1 October 1995'>
     Marge and Homer lose custody of the kids, who are sent to live at the
    Flanders&apos; house.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart Sells His Soul' episode='4' season='7' aired='8 October 1995'>
     When Rev. Lovejoy disciplines Bart for a prank he pulled in church - he
    tricked the organist into playing Iron Butterfly&apos;s
    &quot;&quot;In-A-Gadda-Da-Vida&quot; - he and co-conspirator Milhouse begin
    arguing over whether man really has a soul. Bart scoffs at the notion and
    agrees to &quot;sell&quot; his soul (a piece of paper with the words
    &quot;Bart Simpson&apos;s Soul&quot;) to Milhouse for $5. A series of
    situations makes Bart realize maybe he really did sell his soul, prompting
    him to go all-out to get it back from Milhouse, who isn&apos;t willing to
    sell. Meanwhile, Moe attempts to open a family-style restaurant inside his
    tavern, with the gimmick that if he doesn&apos;t smile when servicing a
    customer, the meal is free. Moe&apos;s surly demeanor and the stress of
    running such a business alone conspire to do the establishment in.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lisa the Vegetarian' episode='5' season='7' aired='15 October 1995'>
     A trip to a local petting zoo convinces Lisa to give up meat, despite
    excessive pressure to convince her not to do so.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror VI' episode='6' season='7' aired='29 October 1995'>
     First, a freak lightning storm causes giant advertising mascots to come to
    life. Next, Groundskeeper Willie dies and swears revenge on the kids in
    their dreams. Finally, Homer accidentally finds himself trapped in another
    dimension.
  </episode>
  <episode title='King Size Homer' episode='7' season='7' aired='5 November 1995'>
     Mr. Burns institutes a new calisthenics program at work. Most employees
    enjoy the morning workout, except Homer, who is too lazy. He finds out that
    if he goes in disability, he will be exempt from the exercises. He finds
    hyper-obesity among the list of disability, so he gorges himself on food to
    balloon up to 300 pounds.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Mother Simpson' episode='8' season='7' aired='19 November 1995'>
     To get out of cleaning a part as community service, Homer fakes his own
    death. When this results in the family&apos;s utilities being cut off, Marge
    puts pressure on him to reveal that he is alive. However, the spurious news
    of his &quot;death&quot; brings his long-lost mother - a hippie who is on
    the run from the law because of her activism against Mr. Burns - back to
    Springfield.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Sideshow Bob&apos;s Last Gleaming' episode='9' season='7' aired='26 November 1995'>
     Sideshow Bob again escapes from prison and takes control of a TV screen at
    an air show, demanding all television stations immediately go off the air.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Simpsons 138th Episode Spectacular' episode='10' season='7' aired='3 December 1995'>
     Troy McClure hosts a retrospective of the first 138 episodes of The
    Simpsons.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Marge Be Not Proud' episode='11' season='7' aired='17 December 1995'>
     Marge&apos;s relationship with Bart is strained when she catches him
    shoplifting before Christmas.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Team Homer' episode='12' season='7' aired='7 January 1996'>
     Homer starts a bowling team with Moe, Apu and Otto, but when Mr. Burns
    discovers the team was funded with his money, he insists on joining.
    Meanwhile, Springfield Elementary introduces uniforms.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Two Bad Neighbors' episode='13' season='7' aired='14 January 1996'>
     To avoid politics, former President George Bush and his wife Barbara retire
    to Springfield, citing its low voter turnout. They quickly become friends to
    the conservative Flanders family, but George soon becomes the enemy of Bart
    and Homer Simpson.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Scenes from the Class Struggle in Springfield' episode='14' season='7' aired='4 February 1996'>
     After Grandpa destroys their television set, the Simpsons go to an outlet
    mall to buy a new one. Marge decides to peruse a clothing store, and buys a
    discounted Chanel suit. A chance encounter with a High School acquaintance,
    while wearing the suit, leads to an invitation to join a country club. Marge
    becomes obsessed with pleasing the club&apos;s upper-class clientele to so
    she can be accepted.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart the Fink' episode='15' season='7' aired='11 February 1996'>
     Bart gets a check he wanted signed by Krusty back stamped. As Krusty was
    supposed to autograph it, Bart wants it taken back to sign, but
    inadvertently reveals Krusty as a tax fraud. Krusty&apos;s lifestyle is
    stripped down to that of an average citizen, his show ruined and most of his
    possessions sold in an auction. Bart is mad at himself, particularly after a
    sobbing Krusty commits suicide by piloting his plane, the
    I&apos;m-Onna-Rolla-Gay, into a mountainside. Bart sees visions of Krusty
    everywhere, but are they illusions or real life?
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lisa the Iconoclast' episode='16' season='7' aired='18 February 1996'>
     Lisa discovers that her town&apos;s beloved founder Jebediah Springfield
    was in fact a vicious pirate.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer the Smithers' episode='17' season='7' aired='25 February 1996'>
     When Smithers is forced to take a vacation, he appoints Homer as his
    temporary replacement.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Day the Violence Died' episode='18' season='7' aired='17 March 1996'>
     Bart &amp; Lisa meet a bum who claims to have created Itchy, one half of
    the cat and mouse team of their favorite cartoon series, &quot;Itchy &amp;
    Scratchy.&quot;
  </episode>
  <episode title='A Fish Called Selma' episode='19' season='7' aired='24 March 1996'>
     Washed-up movie star Troy McClure is pulled over for driving without
    corrective lenses, and forced to go to the DMV to get his eyes checked.
    While there, he meets Selma, who he asks out for dinner. Spotted by a
    reporter, he quickly realizes that being seen in public with a woman will
    grab enough headlines to revitalize his career, leading to a whirlwind
    romance between him and Selma.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart on the Road' episode='20' season='7' aired='31 March 1996'>
     Unable to get out of a mis-scheduled spring vacation, Principal Skinner
    makes up the holiday &quot;Go to Work with Your Parents Day,&quot; giving
    Lisa the chance to spend time with Homer, and Bart the chance to work with
    Patty &amp; Selma at the DMV. When Bart makes his own fake driver&apos;s
    license and Martin wins a bundle at the stock market, Bart rents a car, and
    takes Milhouse, Martin, and Nelson Muntz on a huge road trip.
  </episode>
  <episode title='22 Short Films About Springfield' episode='21' season='7' aired='14 April 1996'>
     A series of vignettes highlights a day in the life of various Springfield
    residents.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Raging Abe Simpson and His Grumbling Grandson in &apos;The Curse of the Flying Hellfish&apos;' episode='22' season='7' aired='28 April 1996'>
     Grandpa Simpson reveals to Bart that he and Montgomery Burns were part of a
    World War 2 unit known as the Flying Hellfish, which stole priceless art
    from a German castle during the war, of which the last surviving member
    would inherit the fortune. When another member of his platoon dies, Abe and
    Burns remain the last two survivors, and Burns vows to make sure Grandpa
    doesn&apos;t become the last Hellfish, until Abe and Bart vow to find the
    fortune before Burns does.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Much Apu About Nothing' episode='23' season='7' aired='5 May 1996'>
     Anti-Immigration fever sweeps Springfield, which threatens to lead to the
    deportation of of Apu, until Homer decides to reject the mob mentality, and
    help him become a legal citizen.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homerpalooza' episode='24' season='7' aired='19 May 1996'>
     Depressed about his inability to keep up with the existing music scene when
    Bart reveals how uncool his interest in 1970&apos;s rock music truly is,
    Homer decides to take Bart and Lisa to the Hullabalooza music festival to
    show them this isn&apos;t the case. Failing at that, he nearly sparks a riot
    and gets shot at with a cannon(ironically for Peter Frampton) which bounces
    a fake pig off his fat belly, and ends up being hired as part of the
    festival&apos;s freak show, touring with bands such as Smashing Pumpkins,
    Cypress Hill, Sonic Youth, and yes, Frampton.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Summer of 4 Ft. 2' episode='25' season='7' aired='19 May 1996'>
     The end of the school year, and an empty yearbook causes Lisa to
    contemplate her lack of popularity. When Ned Flanders is summoned for jury
    duty and offers Homer a chance to stay at his beach house, Lisa sees this as
    the opportunity to reinvent herself as a slacker in the hope of gaining
    friends, which proves to be far more successful than she could possibly
    imagine --- but not if Bart has any say in the matter.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror VII' episode='1' season='8' aired='27 October 1996'>
     Bart discovers his Siamese twin Hugo in the attic. Then, Lisa becomes a god
    after she accidentally creates life in a science fair project. Finally, Kang
    and Kodos plot to conquer the planet disguised as Bill Clinton and Bob Dole.
  </episode>
  <episode title='You Only Move Twice' episode='2' season='8' aired='3 November 1996'>
     Homer takes a new job in a new town. However, his friendly new boss might
    be a super villain bent on world domination.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Homer They Fall' episode='3' season='8' aired='10 November 1996'>
     Homer becomes a boxer after Moe discovers his amazing ability to take a
    punch.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Burns, Baby Burns' episode='4' season='8' aired='17 November 1996'>
     The Simpsons try to reunite Homer&apos;s boss, Mr. Burns, with Larry,
    Burns&apos; long-lost son.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart After Dark' episode='5' season='8' aired='24 November 1996'>
     Marge leads a crusade against a local burlesque house after she discovers
    Bart working there.
  </episode>
  <episode title='A Milhouse Divided' episode='6' season='8' aired='1 December 1996'>
     Milhouse&apos;s parents divorce, leading Homer to question the strength of
    his own marriage.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lisa&apos;s Date with Density' episode='7' season='8' aired='15 December 1996'>
     At school, Nelson is caught with a cache of stolen items in his locker
    (including the &quot;H&quot; hood emblem from Supt. Chalmers&apos; car) and
    is assigned to do chores with Groundskeeper Willie. Lisa is caught observing
    the goings-on and is assigned detention, where she develops a crush on
    Nelson. Lisa tries to reform Nelson, and it works for awhile. However, as
    the old saying goes, you can&apos;t teach a juvenile delinquent new tricks
    and it isn&apos;t long before Nelson is back to his old ways; he and his
    buddies had been caught throwing spoiled food at Skinner&apos;s house and
    tries to lie to Lisa about his participation in the whole thing, but
    ultimately lets slip the truth. Meanwhile, Homer obtains an autodialer and
    decides it will help him make easy money through his &quot;Happy Dude&quot;
    telemarketing scheme. Homer is eventually caught and made to use the
    autodialer to call back everyone he scammed in apology. Which he does ...
    then he asks for more money as part of a &quot;Sorry Dude&quot; scam.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Hurricane Neddy' episode='8' season='8' aired='29 December 1996'>
     A hurricane strikes Springfield, and in its wake, the Flanders&apos; home
    is demolished. Ned becomes depressed, and reassurance from Maude and Rev.
    Lovejoy do little to offset Kent Brockman&apos;s hurricane coverage (where
    he reports that the Leftorium is being looted). Marge then bursts into the
    church where the Flanders are staying and announces a miracle: Ned&apos;s
    home has been rebuilt. Well, sort of ... the house - built by an army of
    volunteers commissioned by Homer - is ill-constructed and quickly falls
    down. Ned then loses his temper and screams at everyone for their shoddy
    workmanship and what he views as their meddling. (Homer thinks he &quot;got
    off easy&quot; when Ned calls him &quot;the worst person I have ever
    met.&quot;) Ned goes for a drive to cool down and heads toward a mental
    institution, where he checks himself in. There, his childhood psychiatrist
    counsels him on his crisis and determines that he has problems appropriately
    expressing his anger. The doctor recruits Homer to help Ned get to the root
    of his frustrations - his parents, who did not do a good job raising him.
    Eventually, Ned is released.
  </episode>
  <episode title='El Viaje Misterioso de Nuestro Homer' episode='9' season='8' aired='5 January 1997'>
     Marge&apos;s fears that Homer will embarrass her at the annual Springfield
    Chili Cook-Off again, are reaffirmed when after tasting various bland
    samples of chili, he comes across a specialty made by Chief Wiggum laced
    with hallucinogenic Guatemalan peppers. The chili sends him on a psychedelic
    journey where he meets an imaginary Coyote spirit guide(voiced by country
    music legend Johnny Cash), who urges him to find his soul mate, causing him
    to doubt that he should&apos;ve ever married Marge in the first place.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Springfield Files' episode='10' season='8' aired='12 January 1997'>
     In yet another crazed crossover, Leonard Nimoy narrates another tale of the
    supernatural, reminiscent of his days with &quot;In Search Of.&quot;
    Realizing that even he&apos;s too drunk to drive after a night at Moe&apos;s
    Tavern, Homer stumbles through the woods and encounters a green glowing
    alien. Needless to say, nobody takes him seriously, except for
    &quot;X-Files&quot; FBI Agent Fox Mulder, who once again drags along his
    partner Dana Scully on another quest to prove the government is hiding the
    presence of UFO&apos;s from the public. However, even this mission may make
    a skeptic out of Mulder.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Twisted World of Marge Simpson' episode='11' season='8' aired='19 January 1997'>
     Marge enters the pretzel vending business, but when she fails, Homer
    recruits some help from the mob.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Mountain of Madness' episode='12' season='8' aired='2 February 1997'>
     Homer and Mr. Burns get trapped in a snowed-in cabin during a company
    retreat.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Simpsoncalifragilisticexpiala-Annoyed-Grunt-cious' episode='13' season='8' aired='7 February 1997'>
     After a little bit of hair loss caused by stress, the Simpson family decide
    that a nanny to help around the house may be a good idea, causing them to
    come into contact with a very odd character named Shary Bobbins.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Itchy &amp; Scratchy &amp; Poochie Show' episode='14' season='8' aired='7 February 1997'>
     Krusty becomes alarmed at the flagging ratings for &quot;The Itchy &amp;
    Scratchy Show&quot; and demands it be corrected. The producers reason some
    new gimmicks are needed to inject fresh air and - after a focus group
    doesn&apos;t quite go as well as planned - decide to introduce a new
    character named Poochie, a rapping cartoon dog that is supposed to become
    friends with Itchy and Scratchy. Homer auditions to do Poochie&apos;s voice
    and wins the part. Poochie&apos;s first cartoon, &quot;The Beagle Has
    Landed,&quot; premieres to great fanfare but is poorly received to say the
    least. The producers decide that, given his spectacular failure, Poochie
    will be killed off in the mutt&apos;s next cartoon. Homer learns about this
    and at his next recording session, gives a speech imploring everyone to give
    Poochie a chance. However, the effort is unsuccessful and Poochie&apos;s
    death - along with the correct lines dubbed in - is revealed in the next
    animated short. Also: A college-aged boy named Roy temporarily moves in with
    the Simpsons and - in a nod to cliched characters being used as a gimmick to
    entice viewership of waning TV shows - does everything to get in the way.
    Eventually, Roy announces he&apos;s moving out and moving in with a pair of
    sexy ladies.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer&apos;s Phobia' episode='15' season='8' aired='16 February 1997'>
     Homer fears that Bart&apos;s masculinity is at stake when he suspects that
    he&apos;s being influenced by a flamboyant homosexual collectible store
    owner named John(Waters). All his efforts to show Bart how to be a man keep
    backfiring on him... or do they?
  </episode>
  <episode title='Brother from Another Series' episode='16' season='8' aired='23 February 1997'>
     Sideshow Bob is released from prison into the custody of his younger
    brother Cecil (voiced by David Hyde Pierce), Springfield&apos;s Chief
    Hydrological Engineer. He works as the foreman on a new hydroelectric dam.
    Bart is convinced that Bob is up to something shady again, and follows him
    everywhere.
  </episode>
  <episode title='My Sister, My Sitter' episode='17' season='8' aired='2 March 1997'>
     Bart is outraged when Lisa becomes his babysitter.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer vs. the 18th Amendment' episode='18' season='8' aired='16 March 1997'>
     Bart gets drunk during a St. Patrick&apos;s Day Parade, provoking the city
    government to enforce a two-hundred year old prohibition law. Rex Banner, an
    Elliot Ness-type character, takes over the police force to help enforce the
    law, since Wiggum failed to do do. Meanwhile, Homer decides to make money
    for himself as a bootlegger, calling himself &quot;The Beer Baron.&quot;
  </episode>
  <episode title='Grade School Confidential' episode='19' season='8' aired='6 April 1997'>
     Martin&apos;s birthday party is predictably dull until nearly all the
    guests become ill with food poisoning. The only ones not to get sick are
    Bart (who didn&apos;t want to eat the spoiled oysters), and Principal
    Skinner and Mrs. Krabappel, who fall in love with each other. Bart catches
    his principal and teacher kissing passionately, but they immediately find
    out and want to swear him to secrecy. They make him his gofer, making his
    life miserable at school and calling him at all hours of the night (all for
    the reward of Milhouse inheriting Bart&apos;s poor school record). Bart
    eventually loses his patience and exposes the Skinner-Krabappel
    relationship. After rumors - most of them grossly exaggerated - begin
    running wild through town, Supt. Chalmers threatens to fire both Principal
    Skinner and Mrs. Krabappel (since the relationship is forbidden per district
    policy) and does when Skinner refuses to call the relationship off.
    Eventually, Bart convinces Skinner to stand up for himself and his new
    girlfriend, and they decide to climb onto the roof and stay there until
    Chalmers reinstates them and accepts their relationship. The effort works,
    and Principal Skinner and Mrs. Krabappel are back at school.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Canine Mutiny' episode='20' season='8' aired='13 April 1997'>
     Using Santa&apos;s Little Helper&apos;s name, Bart is able to fraudulently
    obtain a credit card. Unaware that he needs to eventually pay for
    everything, Bart makes outlandish purchases - including a specially breeded
    collie he names Laddie. He manages to evade Lisa&apos;s demand for an
    explanation but can&apos;t keep back the creditors, who eventually repossess
    everything. When the creditors as for the dog, Bart - who has fallen in love
    with Laddie - sends Santa&apos;s Little Helper with the repo men. Later,
    Bart grows bored with Laddie and gives her to Chief Wiggum; in the
    aftermath, Bart is forced to explain everything and is sent to get
    Santa&apos;s Little Helper back any way he can. Bart eventually tracks down
    the pooch to a blind man&apos;s house and upon collecting Santa&apos;s
    Little Helper begins to leave. However, the blind man is able to trap
    burglar Bart in the closet. When Chief Wiggum comes to arrest Bart, Laddie
    sniffs out marijuana in the blind man&apos;s pocket. Santa&apos;s Little
    Helper goes home with Bart, while Wiggum holds a huge party at the
    man&apos;s house.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Old Man and the Lisa' episode='21' season='8' aired='20 April 1997'>
     Burns loses his fortune and recruits Lisa to help him get it back.
  </episode>
  <episode title='In Marge We Trust' episode='22' season='8' aired='27 April 1997'>
     Marge becomes a church counselor to compensate for Reverend Lovejoy&apos;s
    lack of interest. Meanwhile, Homer discovers a Japanese detergent is using
    his face for their logo.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer&apos;s Enemy' episode='23' season='8' aired='4 May 1997'>
     Mr. Burns hires Frank Grimes (the human interest subject of Kent
    Brockman&apos;s report) as executive vice president at the Springfield
    Nuclear Power Plant. Grimes meets the employees and is immediately stunned
    at Homer&apos;s lackadasial work performance and his co-workers are
    nonchalant about it. Grimes - already annoyed by Homer&apos;s habits -
    becomes horrified when he observes Homer nearly drink a flask containing a
    toxic acid in absent-mindedness; however, Grimes is harshly reprimanded when
    he knocks the vial away and causes damage. Grimes tells Homer that they are
    &quot;enemies,&quot; but Homer - still wanting to be friends - invites
    &quot;Grimey&quot; over for dinner. However, the attempt only makes matters
    worse when Grimes sees that Homer is living in a nice home and has a family.
    Resolved to expose Homer as a fraud once and for all, he hands out a flyer
    announcing a &quot;design your own power plant&quot; contest, which has all
    references to this being a contest for elementary school students. However,
    Homer easily wins the contest, causing Grimes to go crazy. After running
    amok through the plant and mocking Homer, Grimes touches some electrical
    wires and is electrocuted. In the subplot, Bart wanders into public auction
    and submits the winning bid ($1) for an abandoned factory. Bart and Milhouse
    play around inside until the place crumbles.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Simpsons Spin-Off Showcase' episode='24' season='8' aired='11 May 1997'>
     Troy McClure introduces three &quot;potential spin-offs&quot; of The
    Simpsons. The fictional pilots include: &quot;Chief Wiggum, P.I. (Wiggum and
    Principal Skinner are detectives in New Orleans, and must contend with the
    evil Big Daddy, who kidnaps Ralph); &quot;The Love-Matic Grandpa&quot; (a
    spoof of the failed 1960s-era sitcom &quot;My Mother the Car,&quot; where
    Grampa&apos;s ghost inhabits a Love Tester machine at Moe&apos;s Tavern);
    and &quot;The Simpson Family Smile-Time Variety Hour&quot; (the Simpsons -
    along with a teen-aged &quot;Lisa&quot; - star in a comedy-variety show,
    much like the Bradys did in 1977).
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Secret War of Lisa Simpson' episode='25' season='8' aired='18 May 1997'>
     After a prank destroys half the town, Bart is shipped away to military
    school. Lisa, seeking a challenge, decides to enroll with him, but is faced
    with discrimination as the school&apos;s only girl cadet.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The City of New York vs. Homer Simpson' episode='1' season='9' aired='21 September 1997'>
     Homer must travel to New York to get his car back, which is illegally
    parked at World Trade Center Plaza.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Principal and the Pauper' episode='2' season='9' aired='28 September 1997'>
     After holding a surprise tribute to their beloved Elementary school
    principal Skinner, the town of Springfield is shocked to find out that
    Seymour Skinner is an impostor...
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lisa&apos;s Sax' episode='3' season='9' aired='19 October 1997'>
     Homer recounts the story of Bart&apos;s first day of school, which
    corresponds with the story of how Lisa got her saxophone.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror VIII' episode='4' season='9' aired='26 October 1997'>
     In &quot;The Homega Man,&quot; Homer battles mutants after Springfield is
    annihilated by a neutron bomb. Then, Bart has his DNA mixed with a fly in
    &quot;Fly vs. Fly.&quot; Finally, Marge is revealed to be a witch in
    colonial Springfield in &quot;Easy Bake Coven.&quot;
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Cartridge Family' episode='5' season='9' aired='2 November 1997'>
     After a massive soccer riot, Homer decides to invest in a home security
    system but can&apos;t afford the high price. He does the next best thing: He
    purchases a gun. This is despite Marge&apos;s stern opposition to having a
    gun. Homer plays with the gun like a toy and almost causes an accident at
    the dinner table. Marge warns Homer to get rid of the gun now; Homer agrees,
    but Bart finds the gun later in the refrigerator. Marge sees this, takes the
    gun away and tells Homer she is taking the kids and moving out. Homer
    eventually is kicked out of the local NRA chapter (for his careless use of
    the gun), and decides he needs to try to get Marge back. Eventually, he
    manages to foil Snake&apos;s armed robbery at the hotel where Marge is
    staying. Homer finally gets rid of the gun, but Marge decides to keep it for
    herself.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart Star' episode='6' season='9' aired='9 November 1997'>
     A pee-wee football team forms as a solution to Springfield&apos;s growing
    childhood obesity crisis. When Homer takes over as coach after causing
    Flanders to quit, he tries to make Bart the star of the team despite his
    poor performance on the field.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Two Mrs. Nahasapeemapetilons' episode='7' season='9' aired='16 November 1997'>
     Marge must pose as Apu&apos;s wife to prevent his upcoming arranged
    marriage.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lisa the Skeptic' episode='8' season='9' aired='23 November 1997'>
     Another day at Springfield Elementary School, another field trip - this
    time to an archaeological dig. During the dig, Lisa unearths what appears to
    be a fossilized human skeleton with wings.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Realty Bites' episode='9' season='9' aired='7 December 1997'>
     Marge becomes a real-estate agent.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Miracle on Evergreen Terrace' episode='10' season='9' aired='21 December 1997'>
     On Christmas Eve, Marge admonishes the family not to open presents until 7
    a.m. the next morning. Bart finds a way around the directive and opens his
    gifts at 5 a.m. However, his prized gift - a remote-controlled fire truck -
    overheats and causes a fire that engulfs the tree and presents. The family
    investigates and Bart tells them that a burglar has struck. As a result of
    Kent Brockman&apos;s human interest story, the entire town donates gifts and
    cash to the Simpsons for their &quot;misfortune.&quot; Eventually, Bart
    admits the truth, angering his clueless family but angering the town even
    more (when Brockman finds out the truth). The family is made into outcasts,
    and Marge&apos;s attempt to win the needed funds on &quot;Jeopardy!&quot;
    (to pay everybody back) fails miserably. Eventually, the townspeople loot
    the Simpsons&apos; home ... save for a dust rag.
  </episode>
  <episode title='All Singing, All Dancing' episode='11' season='9' aired='4 January 1998'>
     Homer is disappointed when the western he rented turns out to be a musical,
    so the family reminds him of the musical moments in the show&apos;s history.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart Carny' episode='12' season='9' aired='11 January 1998'>
     Bart and Homer befriend two carnies and invite them to stay with them, but
    the carnies soon swindle the Simpsons out of their house.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Joy of Sect' episode='13' season='9' aired='8 February 1998'>
     An evil cult called the Movementarians brainwashes the citizens of
    Springfield and it&apos;s up to Marge to get them back.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Das Bus' episode='14' season='9' aired='15 February 1998'>
     The kids get stranded on a desert island in a parody of Lord Of The Flies.
    Meanwhile, Homer attempts to cash in on the Internet.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Last Temptation of Krust' episode='15' season='9' aired='22 February 1998'>
     After a disastrous performance, Krusty changes his image and becomes an
    edgy stand-up.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Dumbbell Indemnity' episode='16' season='9' aired='1 March 1998'>
     Homer and Moe attempt insurance fraud so that Moe can support his new
    girlfriend. When Homer ends up in jail, Moe has to decide whether or not
    come forward.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lisa the Simpson' episode='17' season='9' aired='8 March 1998'>
     Lisa fears she is losing her intelligence when she learns about the fabled
    Simpson gene. Meanwhile, Jasper freezes himself in the Kwik-E-Mart freezer.
  </episode>
  <episode title='This Little Wiggy' episode='18' season='9' aired='22 March 1998'>
     Bart is reluctant to hang out with Ralph Wiggum, until he gains access to
    Chief Wiggum&apos;s master key to the city.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Simpson Tide' episode='19' season='9' aired='29 March 1998'>
     Homer causes an international incident after he joins the Naval reserves.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Trouble with Trillions' episode='20' season='9' aired='5 April 1998'>
     Homer is forced to spy for the IRS after an audit. But when he is asked to
    retrieve a trillion dollar bill from Mr. Burns, he switches sides and the
    two flee to Cuba for refuge.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Girly Edition' episode='21' season='9' aired='19 April 1998'>
     Bart in Lisa become locked in competition when they anchor a
    children&apos;s news program. Meanwhile, Homer adopts a helper monkey.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Trash of the Titans' episode='22' season='9' aired='26 April 1998'>
     After a feud with the Springfield refuse collectors, Homer decides to run
    for Sanitation Commisioner
  </episode>
  <episode title='King of the Hill' episode='23' season='9' aired='3 May 1998'>
     After humiliating Bart at a church picnic, Homer resolves to get in shape.
    Soon, he is contacted by an energy bar company that wants him to climb a
    mountain as a promotion.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lost Our Lisa' episode='24' season='9' aired='10 May 1998'>
     Lisa gets lost after she tries to take a bus to a museum.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Natural Born Kissers' episode='25' season='9' aired='17 May 1998'>
     Homer and Marge&apos;s attempt to spice up their marriage leads to the
    couple being chased naked through Springfield.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lard of the Dance' episode='1' season='10' aired='23 August 1998'>
     Lisa organizes a dance at her school, while Homer and Bart try to start
    their own &quot;grease business&quot;
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Wizard of Evergreen Terrace' episode='2' season='10' aired='20 September 1998'>
     Homer&apos;s midlife crisis leads to a disastrous attempt at being an
    inventor.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart the Mother' episode='3' season='10' aired='27 September 1998'>
     When Bart accidentally kills a mother bird, he tries to make amends by
    raising the eggs.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror IX' episode='4' season='10' aired='25 October 1998'>
     Homer receives an evil hair transplant in &quot;Hell Toupee.&quot; Then,
    Bart and Lisa get trapped in an Itchy and Scratchy cartoon in &quot;The
    Terror Of Tiny Toon.&quot; Finally, Maggie is revealed to be an alien in
    &quot;Starship Poopers.&quot;
  </episode>
  <episode title='When You Dish Upon a Star' episode='5' season='10' aired='8 November 1998'>
     Homer becomes a Hollywood insider when he befriends Alec Baldwin and Kim
    Basinger.
  </episode>
  <episode title='D&apos;oh-in&apos; in the Wind' episode='6' season='10' aired='15 November 1998'>
     Homer becomes a hippie after a revelation about his middle name.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lisa Gets an A' episode='7' season='10' aired='22 November 1998'>
     Lisa cheats on a test and has a moral crisis when her perfect score
    qualifies the school for grant money. Meanwhile, Homer can&apos;t bring
    himself to cook a lobster, so he adopts it as a pet instead.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer Simpson in: Kidney Trouble' episode='8' season='10' aired='6 December 1998'>
     Homer gets cold feet before an operation that could save Grampa&apos;s
    life.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Mayored to the Mob' episode='9' season='10' aired='20 December 1998'>
     Homer deals with corruption when he becomes Mayor Quimby&apos;s bodyguard.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Viva Ned Flanders' episode='10' season='10' aired='10 January 1999'>
     When Homer takes Ned to Las Vegas in an attempt to get him to loosen up,
    the pair end up marrying cocktail waitresses in a drunken haze.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Wild Barts Can&apos;t Be Broken' episode='11' season='10' aired='17 January 1999'>
     The children of Springfield revolt after a curfew is enforced.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Sunday, Cruddy Sunday' episode='12' season='10' aired='31 January 1999'>
     Homer and his friends head to the Superbowl, but are forced to sneak in
    when they discover their tickets are counterfeit.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer to the Max' episode='13' season='10' aired='7 February 1999'>
     After a dimwitted TV character is coincidentally named Homer Simpson, Homer
    changes his name to Max Power.
  </episode>
  <episode title='I&apos;m with Cupid' episode='14' season='10' aired='14 February 1999'>
     The husbands of Springfield plot revenge after Apu outshines them on
    Valentine&apos;s Day.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Marge Simpson in &apos;Screaming Yellow Honkers&apos;' episode='15' season='10' aired='21 February 1999'>
     Marge&apos;s new SUV gives her a potent case of road rage.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Make Room for Lisa' episode='16' season='10' aired='28 February 1999'>
     When Homer installs a cell phone tower on his roof to pay for his
    destruction of the Bill Of Rights, the machinery is put in Lisa&apos;s room,
    forcing her to move in with Bart. When the new living arrangement causes her
    stress, Homer agrees to try sensory deprivation therapy with her.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Maximum Homerdrive' episode='17' season='10' aired='28 March 1999'>
     Homer finishes a cross country delivery that a trucker died before
    completing, taking Bart along for the ride. Marge and Lisa experience
    problems with the novelty doorbell they purchased.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Simpsons Bible Stories' episode='18' season='10' aired='4 April 1999'>
     Three famous religious stories are retold Simpsons style as the family nods
    off at church.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Mom and Pop Art' episode='19' season='10' aired='11 April 1999'>
     Homer becomes the talk of the Springfield art community when a failed
    barbecue pit he worked on is mistaken for an art project.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Old Man and the &apos;C&apos; Student' episode='20' season='10' aired='25 April 1999'>
     Bart is punished with community service at the Retirement Castle after he
    ruins Springfield&apos;s chances of hosting the Olympics.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Monty Can&apos;t Buy Me Love' episode='21' season='10' aired='2 May 1999'>
     Mr. Burns attempts to be popular by capturing the Loch Ness Monster.
  </episode>
  <episode title='They Saved Lisa&apos;s Brain' episode='22' season='10' aired='9 May 1999'>
     Lisa is invited to join the Springfield chapter of MENSA and the group ends
    up running the city. Meanwhile Homer poses for erotic photos.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Thirty Minutes Over Tokyo' episode='23' season='10' aired='16 May 1999'>
     The Simpsons must perform on a Japanese game show after Homer loses their
    money on a vacation.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Beyond Blunderdome' episode='1' season='11' aired='26 September 1999'>
     When Mel Gibson becomes convinced that Homer is the only man with the guts
    to tell him the truth, he insists Homer accompany him to Hollywood to help
    fix his newest film project, a remake of Mr. Smith Goes to Washington.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Brother&apos;s Little Helper' episode='2' season='11' aired='3 October 1999'>
     Bart is put on medication to control his behavior, but the pills cause him
    to become paranoid and insane.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Guess Who&apos;s Coming to Criticize Dinner?' episode='3' season='11' aired='24 October 1999'>
     Homer&apos;s negative reviews as a food critic puts his life in danger.
    Fortunately he has Lisa fighting for him.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror X' episode='4' season='11' aired='31 October 1999'>
     The Simpsons attempt to cover up their accidental murder of Ned Flanders in
    &quot;I Know What You Did-Iddly-Did.&quot; Then, Bart and Lisa become
    superheroes and save Lucy Lawless from the evil Collector in
    &quot;Desperately Xeeking Xena.&quot; Finally, Homer&apos;s incompetence
    causes a Y2K apocalypse in &quot;Life&apos;s A Glitch, Then You Die.&quot;
  </episode>
  <episode title='E-I-E-I-(Annoyed Grunt)' episode='5' season='11' aired='7 November 1999'>
     Homer cowards out of a pistol-duel and hides out with the rest of the
    family on a country farm.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Hello Gutter, Hello Fadder' episode='6' season='11' aired='14 November 1999'>
     Homer becomes a minor celebrity around Springfield after bowling a perfect
    game.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Eight Misbehavin&apos;' episode='7' season='11' aired='21 November 1999'>
     Apu struggles with fatherhood after Manjula gives birth to octuplets.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Take My Wife, Sleaze' episode='8' season='11' aired='28 November 1999'>
     Homer&apos;s attempt at creating a motorcycle gang attracts a real gang,
    who kidnap Marge.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Grift of the Magi' episode='9' season='11' aired='19 December 1999'>
     A toy company purchases Springfield Elementary and uses the student body as
    a focus group for their new Christmas toy Funzo.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Little Big Mom' episode='10' season='11' aired='9 January 2000'>
     Lisa finds out how rough Marge has it when her mom is in traction and she
    becomes the woman of the house. Homer and Bart&apos;s antics get her so
    worked up she conspires to teach them a lesson.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Faith Off' episode='11' season='11' aired='16 January 2000'>
     Bart is led to believe he has special healing powers after a tent revival.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Mansion Family' episode='12' season='11' aired='23 January 2000'>
     When Mr. Burns has to go the Mayo Clinic in Minnesota for a checkup, he
    chooses The Simpsons to take care of his mansion while he is gone. Homer and
    his friends take Mr. Burns yacht into international waters, where they end
    up being targeted by modern day pirates.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Saddlesore Galactica' episode='13' season='11' aired='6 February 2000'>
     The Simpsons get an abused horse and make him a contender in horse racing.
    Homer finds out a secret conspiracy about jockeys. Lisa tries to reach
    President Clinton when the results of a school band talent competition seem
    tainted.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Alone Again, Natura-Diddly' episode='14' season='11' aired='13 February 2000'>
     Ned deals with his grief after Maude&apos;s untimely death.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Missionary: Impossible' episode='15' season='11' aired='20 February 2000'>
     When Homer is wanted dead for reneging on a 10,000 dollar pledge to PBS,
    Reverend Lovejoy sets him up for missionary work in the South Pacific until
    the heat dies down.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Pygmoelian' episode='16' season='11' aired='27 February 2000'>
     Plastic surgery not only transforms Moe the Bartender from ugly to hunky,
    it helps gets him a job on a hit daytime drama.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart to the Future' episode='17' season='11' aired='19 March 2000'>
     Bart gets a glimpse of the future while the family is on vacation at an
    Indian casino.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Days of Wine and D&apos;oh&apos;ses' episode='18' season='11' aired='9 April 2000'>
     Homer doesn&apos;t like it when Barney quits drinking; Bart and Lisa get
    into trouble when they enter a photo contest for the new phone book cover.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Kill the Alligator and Run' episode='19' season='11' aired='30 April 2000'>
     The Simpsons become wanted criminals after injuring a famous alligator
    during a Florida vacation.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Last Tap Dance in Springfield' episode='20' season='11' aired='7 May 2000'>
     Lisa has difficulties learning to tap dance. Meanwhile Bart and Milhouse
    ditch summer camp to spend a week living in the mall.
  </episode>
  <episode title='It&apos;s a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad Marge' episode='21' season='11' aired='14 May 2000'>
     Everybody loves the new Simpsons&apos; house guest Becky. Except Marge, who
    thinks Becky wants to kill her.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Behind the Laughter' episode='22' season='11' aired='21 May 2000'>
     The Simpsons discuss their fame in a behind the scenes look at the show.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror XI' episode='1' season='12' aired='1 November 2000'>
     Homer must do one good deed to get into Heaven in &quot;G-G-Ghost
    D-D-Dad.&quot; Then, Bart and Lisa encounter a witch in a gingerbread house
    in &quot;Scary Tales Can Come True.&quot; Finally, super-intelligent
    dolphins strike back at humanity in &quot;Night Of The Dolphin.&quot;
  </episode>
  <episode title='A Tale of Two Springfields' episode='2' season='12' aired='5 November 2000'>
     When Homer tries to enter a phone-in competition, he becomes terribly
    stubborn and angry for Springfield introducing a new dialing code. In the
    Town Hall, after the Mayor&apos;s meeting about the change, Homer discovers
    that all the rich people live on one side of Springfield, with the old code,
    and Homer is left to try and manage with the new code. However, he protests,
    and ends up splitting Springfield into Old and New. Homer desperately tries
    different ways to tackle Old Springfield, but in doing so, he only makes
    them richer when they discover gold at the bottom of the river. Homer
    finally builds a large wall to separate the two sides, and remembers that
    The Who are planned to stage at Springfield for a concert. Will Homer manage
    to convince The Who to play on his side of town instead of the other&apos;s?
  </episode>
  <episode title='Insane Clown Poppy' episode='3' season='12' aired='12 November 2000'>
     After he learns he has a daughter (Sophie), Krusty turns to Homer for
    parenting advice.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lisa the Tree Hugger' episode='4' season='12' aired='19 November 2000'>
     Lisa&apos;s crush on an environmental activist inspires her to live in a
    tree threatened by loggers.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer vs. Dignity' episode='5' season='12' aired='26 November 2000'>
     Desperate for money, Homer accepts payment from Mr. Burns in exchange for
    humiliating himself.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Computer Wore Menace Shoes' episode='6' season='12' aired='3 December 2000'>
     Homer&apos;s gossip website becomes a huge hit, but when his information
    runs out he resorts to making up news.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Great Money Caper' episode='7' season='12' aired='10 December 2000'>
     The whole town of Springfield conspires to teach Homer and and Bart a
    lesson after the two begin running confidence scams.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Skinner&apos;s Sense of Snow' episode='8' season='12' aired='17 December 2000'>
     A snowstorm traps the kids and Principal Skinner in the school for
    Christmas vacation.
  </episode>
  <episode title='HOMR' episode='9' season='12' aired='7 January 2001'>
     An x-ray reveals a crayon lodged in Homer&apos;s brain. After the crayon is
    removed, Homer experiences a sudden surge in intelligence, making him closer
    to Lisa and isolated from his friends.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Pokey Mom' episode='10' season='12' aired='14 January 2001'>
     Marge befriends a convict with an artistic streak. Meanwhile, Homer battles
    the chiropractic industry after he creates a miracle back pain cure.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Worst Episode Ever' episode='11' season='12' aired='4 February 2001'>
     Bart and Milhouse are left in charge of the comic book store after Comic
    Book Guy is hospitalized.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Tennis the Menace' episode='12' season='12' aired='11 February 2001'>
     Homer installs a tennis court in the backyard, but his lousy playing
    creates a rift in the family.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Day of the Jackanapes' episode='13' season='12' aired='18 February 2001'>
     Sideshow Bob returns with a plan to brainwash Bart and kill Krusty.
  </episode>
  <episode title='New Kids on the Blecch' episode='14' season='12' aired='25 February 2001'>
     Bart, Nelson, Millhouse, and Ralph are recruited by a man named L.T. Smash
    to be in a boy band called the Party Posse but when Lisa discovers the true
    identity of LT. Smash as a navy recruitment officer she tries to tell Homer
    and Marge with hilarious results.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Hungry Hungry Homer' episode='15' season='12' aired='4 March 2001'>
     Homer decides to help his family with all their problems, complaining to
    the Blocko land and other places to claim what is right. But, when Homer
    goes to complain at Springfield Stadium, he secretly discovers that the
    manager is planning to move the team to the Albuquerque Isotopes. After
    Homer is knocked out of remembering the events, he returns to the stadium
    and starts a protest that he will not eat anything until the manager reveals
    the secret. However, the manager and the Duff Man have other plans for
    Homer...
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bye Bye Nerdie' episode='16' season='12' aired='11 March 2001'>
     Problems with a bully lead Lisa to examine just what makes bullies
    aggressive. Meanwhile, Homer gets into the baby-proofing business.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Simpson Safari' episode='17' season='12' aired='1 April 2001'>
     The Simpsons win a trip to Africa.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Trilogy of Error' episode='18' season='12' aired='29 April 2001'>
     The lives of Homer, Lisa and Bart have been split up in a
    less-than-ordinary day, and as each of their problems unfold, their lives
    intertwine on a road of chaos and mayhem all over Springfield. Homer&apos;s
    thumb is accidentally sliced off, and he tries to find a way to the
    hospital; Lisa must find a way to get to the Science fair at school; and
    Bart and Milhouse discover more than just fireworks in a secret cave...
  </episode>
  <episode title='I&apos;m Goin&apos; to Praiseland' episode='19' season='12' aired='6 May 2001'>
     With Homer&apos;s help, Ned Flanders tries to establish a Christian theme
    park based on drawings in his deceased wife&apos;s sketch book.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Children of a Lesser Clod' episode='20' season='12' aired='13 May 2001'>
     After a debilitating injury forces him to stay indoors, Homer begins a
    daycare center.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Simpson Tall Tales' episode='21' season='12' aired='20 May 2001'>
     A hobo tells the Simpsons tall tales on a train ride to Delaware. In the
    first story, Homer is outcast from society as Paul Bunyan. Then, Lisa
    travels the country planting trees as Connie Appleseed. Finally, Bart and
    Nelson raft down the Mississippi as Tom Sawyer and Huck Finn.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror XII' episode='1' season='13' aired='6 November 2001'>
     A gypsy puts a curse on Homer in &quot;Hex In The City.&quot; Then, The
    Simpsons&apos; new automated house malfunctions and tries to kill Homer.
    Finally, Bart and Lisa attend a school for wizards in &quot;Wiz Kids.&quot;
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Parent Rap' episode='2' season='13' aired='11 November 2001'>
     After Bart takes a joyride in a police car, a judge orders him to be
    tethered to Homer at all times.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer the Moe' episode='3' season='13' aired='18 November 2001'>
     Homer and his friends are forced to drink in the Simpsons&apos; garage
    after Moe the Bartender renovates his shady bar into a hipster hangout.
  </episode>
  <episode title='A Hunka Hunka Burns in Love' episode='4' season='13' aired='2 December 2001'>
     Mr. Burns falls in love with a younger woman and recruits Homer to help him
    impress her.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Blunder Years' episode='5' season='13' aired='9 December 2001'>
     A hypnotist uncovers a traumatic experience from Homer&apos;s childhood.
  </episode>
  <episode title='She of Little Faith' episode='6' season='13' aired='16 December 2001'>
     Feeling her church cares more about making money then helping people, Lisa
    drops Christianity for Buddhism.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Brawl in the Family' episode='7' season='13' aired='6 January 2002'>
     A social services officer brings unity to the Simpson family, but their
    newfound happiness is threatened when the cocktail waitress Homer married in
    Vegas shows up at their door.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Sweets and Sour Marge' episode='8' season='13' aired='20 January 2002'>
     Marge rallies for a ban on sugar after Springfield is declared
    America&apos;s fattest city.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Jaws Wired Shut' episode='9' season='13' aired='27 January 2002'>
     Marge can&apos;t deal with the quiet after Homer has his jaws wired shut.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Half-Decent Proposal' episode='10' season='13' aired='10 February 2002'>
     Marge&apos;s high school sweetheart Artie Ziff returns and offers Homer a
    million dollars to spend a weekend with Marge.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Bart Wants What It Wants' episode='11' season='13' aired='17 February 2002'>
     Bart breaks up with his new girlfriend Greta, but gets jealous when she
    begins dating Milhouse.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Lastest Gun in the West' episode='12' season='13' aired='24 February 2002'>
     Bart meets a retired cowboy movie star and convinces him to make a comeback
    on The Krusty the Clown Show.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Old Man and the Key' episode='13' season='13' aired='10 March 2002'>
     Abe gets his driver&apos;s license back to impress a new woman at the
    retirement home.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Tales from the Public Domain' episode='14' season='13' aired='17 March 2002'>
     The family reads stories from a long overdue library book. First, Homer
    (Odysseus) struggles to find his way home after the Trojan War. Next, Lisa
    (Joan Of Arc) leads the French army after hearing the voice of God. Finally,
    Bart (Hamlet) avenges the murder of his father.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Blame It on Lisa' episode='15' season='13' aired='31 March 2002'>
     Lisa sponsors an orphan in Brazil, and when he goes missing she convinces
    the family to go to Brazil to find him. While there, Homer is kidnapped.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Weekend at Burnsie&apos;s' episode='16' season='13' aired='7 April 2002'>
     After a traumatizing eye injury, Homer becomes a habitual user of medical
    marijuana.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Gump Roast' episode='17' season='13' aired='21 April 2002'>
     In this clip show, the citizens of Springfield honor Homer Simpsons with a
    Roast, but the festivities take a turn for the worst when aliens crash it.
  </episode>
  <episode title='I Am Furious Yellow' episode='18' season='13' aired='28 April 2002'>
     Bart&apos;s comic about Homer becomes a hit on-line, prompting Homer to
    attempt to control his anger.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Sweetest Apu' episode='19' season='13' aired='5 May 2002'>
     Apu&apos;s marriage is on the rocks after Manjula finds out he cheated on
    her.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Little Girl in the Big Ten' episode='20' season='13' aired='12 May 2002'>
     Lisa pretends to be a college student and loses favor with her classmates
    at Springfield Elementary in the process. A mysterious illness forces Bart
    to live in a plastic bubble.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Frying Game' episode='21' season='13' aired='19 May 2002'>
     Homer and Marge find themselves on death row after they are framed for
    murder.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Poppa&apos;s Got a Brand New Badge' episode='22' season='13' aired='22 May 2002'>
     Homer becomes chief of police after a scandal forces Wiggum out.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror XIII' episode='1' season='14' aired='3 November 2002'>
     First, Homer uses a magic hammock to clone himself in &quot;Send In The
    Clones.&quot; Then, gun-wielding zombies attack Springfield after a ban on
    firearms in &quot;The Right To Creep And Scare Harms.&quot; Finally, The
    Simpsons are trapped on an island where people are transformed into animals
    in &quot;The Island Of Dr. Hibbert.&quot;
  </episode>
  <episode title='How I Spent My Strummer Vacation' episode='2' season='14' aired='10 November 2002'>
     When Marge, Lisa and Bart find out how hard Homer struggles to keep a roof
    over their heads, they enroll him in a Rock &amp; Roll fantasy camp to relax
    at for a week.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart vs. Lisa vs. the Third Grade' episode='3' season='14' aired='17 November 2002'>
     Bart and Lisa are respectively held back and moved forward one grade,
    putting them in the same class.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Large Marge' episode='4' season='14' aired='24 November 2002'>
     Marge accidentally gets breast implants.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Helter Shelter' episode='5' season='14' aired='1 December 2002'>
     After Lisa brings home the stick of a pro hockey player for yelling at him
    to shoot between the goalie&apos;s legs, the Simpsons&apos; house is eaten
    by termites. To get a home, the family joins a reality show, where they must
    live like a family from 1895.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Great Louse Detective' episode='6' season='14' aired='15 December 2002'>
     Homer has to use Sideshow Bob in order to track down a potential assassin.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Special Edna' episode='7' season='14' aired='5 January 2003'>
     After Skinner once again has let Mrs. Krabappel down, Bart takes her to the
    cinema. To cheer her up, Bart nominates Krabappel for the &apos;teacher of
    the year&apos; award. The nominations is accepted, and soon the Simpsons
    family and Mrs. Krabappel are going to the award ceremony in Orlando,
    Florida, where Skinner tries to get back Krabappel by asking her to marry
    him.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Dad Who Knew Too Little' episode='8' season='14' aired='12 January 2003'>
     Homer hires a private detective to learn more about Lisa.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Strong Arms of the Ma' episode='9' season='14' aired='2 February 2003'>
     Marge takes up body-building to boost her self-esteem after a mugging, but
    the family finds they just can&apos;t cope with a Marge that can bench-press
    500 pounds.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Pray Anything' episode='10' season='14' aired='9 February 2003'>
     Homer turns to religion to help him get what he wants, and is soon awarded
    the church in an injury settlement. Homer then turns the church into his
    personal party pad, and Reverend Lovejoy leaves Springfield to wallow in its
    hedonism.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Barting Over' episode='11' season='14' aired='16 February 2003'>
     When Bart finds out Homer has used all the money Bart got for doing a
    commercial when he was a baby, he moves out of the house and into the same
    building as famous skateboarder, Tony Hawk, whose skateboarding tour Bart
    joins.
  </episode>
  <episode title='I&apos;m Spelling as Fast as I Can' episode='12' season='14' aired='16 February 2003'>
     Lisa participates in the Spellympics, but Homer is busy traveling
    cross-country as Krusty Burger test-markets a new sandwich. Lisa is
    confident that she will win, until she learns that the contest is rigged
    against her.
  </episode>
  <episode title='A Star Is Born Again' episode='13' season='14' aired='2 March 2003'>
     Ned Flanders starts dating a the famous movie star, Sara Sloane, but Ned
    has difficulties with the tabloids following them everywhere.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Mr. Spritz Goes to Washington' episode='14' season='14' aired='9 March 2003'>
     The family makes Krusty run for Congress because of air traffic being
    redirected to fly dangerously close to their house.
  </episode>
  <episode title='C. E. D&apos;oh' episode='15' season='14' aired='16 March 2003'>
     Homer takes over the power plant after tricking Mr. Burns into making him
    the official owner of the power plant.
  </episode>
  <episode title='&apos;Scuse Me While I Miss the Sky' episode='16' season='14' aired='30 March 2003'>
     Lisa becomes interested in astronomy and starts fighting the light
    pollution which is preventing her from being able to enjoy her new hobby.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Three Gays of the Condo' episode='17' season='14' aired='13 April 2003'>
     Finding an old note, Homer discovers Marge secretly hated him many years
    back. Upset, he leaves the house and moves in with two gays.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Dude, Where&apos;s My Ranch?' episode='18' season='14' aired='27 April 2003'>
     Homer&apos;s song, &quot;Everybody Hates Ned Flanders&quot;, becomes a hit
    in Springfield, but the family leaves Springfield to live a couple of weeks
    in a ranch to escape Homer&apos;s song.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Old Yeller-Belly' episode='19' season='14' aired='4 May 2003'>
     Homer throws out Santa&apos;s Little Helper for not saving him from a fire,
    but soon the dog becomes Duff&apos;s new mascot.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Brake My Wife, Please' episode='20' season='14' aired='11 May 2003'>
     Because of Homer losing his driver&apos;s license, Marge has to drive
    everyone everywhere, which is so stressful for her that she accidentally
    runs over Homer leading to the two seeing a marriage counselor.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Bart of War' episode='21' season='14' aired='18 May 2003'>
     Marge makes Bart quit hanging out with Milhouse after the two are caught
    invading the Flanders&apos; home. She then starts a peer group based around
    Native American life for Bart, Nelson, Ralph and Database to participate in.
    When Bart finds out Milhouse has joined a different peer group, they soon
    are at odds as they see whose group can do more community service around
    Springfield.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Moe Baby Blues' episode='22' season='14' aired='18 May 2003'>
     After the blooming of a huge plant in Springfield&apos;s botanic gardens
    causes a stinking fume to spread across town, all the Springfieldians take
    their cars and drive away from the city. When the traffic is jammed on a
    bridge, Homer falls asleep. When he accelerates, he crashes into another car
    and Maggie is sent flying out the open roof window. In the mean time, Moe is
    about to commit suicide by jumping off the same bridge, which is prevented
    by Maggie falling into his arms. He then becomes crazily obsessed by the
    baby.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror XIV' episode='1' season='15' aired='2 November 2003'>
     First, Homer kills the Grim Reaper and takes his place in Reaper Madness.
    Then, Professor Frink&apos;s father is revived, only to kill people and
    steal their organs in Frinkenstein. Finally, Bart and Milhouse get a stop
    watch that can stop time in Stop the World, I Want To Goof Off.
  </episode>
  <episode title='My Mother the Carjacker' episode='2' season='15' aired='9 November 2003'>
     Homer&apos;s mother returns to Springfield, and the city pardons her from
    the charges against her. Mr Burns is furious about this and makes a plan to
    get Mona Simpson in prison.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The President Wore Pearls' episode='3' season='15' aired='16 November 2003'>
     Lisa feuds with Principal Skinner after being elected school president.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Regina Monologues' episode='4' season='15' aired='23 November 2003'>
     Prime minister Tony Blair welcomes the Simpsons to England where they run
    into author J.K. Rowling and actor Ian McKellen.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Fat and the Furriest' episode='5' season='15' aired='30 November 2003'>
     At the dump Homer is videotaped while being attacked by a bear. The town
    regards him a coward, so Homer decides to strike back at the bear.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Today, I Am a Clown' episode='6' season='15' aired='7 December 2003'>
     Krusty decides to do what he never did when he was thirteen years old -
    have a Bar Mitzvah.
  </episode>
  <episode title='&apos;Tis the Fifteenth Season' episode='7' season='15' aired='14 December 2003'>
     After spending all his money on an expensive gift for himself, the family
    thinks Homer should be less of an egoist. Therefore he tries replacing Ned
    Flanders as the &apos;good guy&apos; in town.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Marge vs. Singles, Seniors, Childless Couples and Teens, and Gays' episode='8' season='15' aired='4 January 2004'>
     A concert for babies ends in a riot, so the childless adults of Springfield
    gather to make the town less child-friendly. Of course Marge is against this
    proposition, so she forms her own group to prevent a yes on proposition 242.
  </episode>
  <episode title='I, (Annoyed Grunt)-Bot' episode='9' season='15' aired='11 January 2004'>
     While Lisa and Marge have trouble finding a successor for Snowball II,
    Homer pretends to be a robot and fights robot races to win Bart&apos;s
    affection.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Diatribe of a Mad Housewife' episode='10' season='15' aired='25 January 2004'>
     Marge is inspired to write a novel, but the storyline of the book (a fat,
    mean husband, and a handsome, sweet neighbor) makes Homer jealous.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Margical History Tour' episode='11' season='15' aired='8 February 2004'>
     Marge tells Lisa, Bart and Millhouse three history stories because the
    library doesn&apos;t have any.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Milhouse Doesn&apos;t Live Here Anymore' episode='12' season='15' aired='15 February 2004'>
     Milhouse moves to Capital City, and therefore Lisa and Bart become best
    friends.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Smart &amp; Smarter' episode='13' season='15' aired='22 February 2004'>
     When Maggie was revealed to have an IQ of 167, Lisa is no longer the genius
    of the family, causing a rivalry between the sisters.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Ziff Who Came to Dinner' episode='14' season='15' aired='14 March 2004'>
     Artie Ziff turns out to be hiding out in the attic of the Simpsons.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Co-Dependent&apos;s Day' episode='15' season='15' aired='21 March 2004'>
     Marge takes up heavy drinking to spend more time with Homer. Bart and Lisa
    confront a famous movie director about the drop in quality his films have
    taken.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Wandering Juvie' episode='16' season='15' aired='28 March 2004'>
     After playing a prank on the whole town, Bart is sentenced to six months of
    juvenile detention. There he meets Gina, who forces Bart to escape with her.
  </episode>
  <episode title='My Big Fat Geek Wedding' episode='17' season='15' aired='18 April 2004'>
     Mrs. Krabapel falls for Comic Book Guy and they plan a Star Trek like
    wedding. Principal Skinner plans to prevent it.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Catch &apos;Em If You Can' episode='18' season='15' aired='25 April 2004'>
     Homer and Marge try to have a vacation without the kids but Bart and Lisa
    follow them everywhere they go.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Simple Simpson' episode='19' season='15' aired='2 May 2004'>
     Homer becomes a costumed vigilante who uses pies for weapons after
    witnessing Lisa get humiliated at a competition at the state fair.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Way We Weren&apos;t' episode='20' season='15' aired='9 May 2004'>
     Marge and Homer find out that they actually kissed each other at age 10
    without knowing they were each other&apos;s first kisses, and tell the story
    about this.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart-Mangled Banner' episode='21' season='15' aired='16 May 2004'>
     An accidental photo showing Bart mooning the American flag makes the
    Simpsons the most hated family in town.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Fraudcast News' episode='22' season='15' aired='23 May 2004'>
     Lisa makes her own newspaper for publishing poems and such, and at the same
    time Mr Burns decides to buy every media in town to improve his image. In
    the end Lisa&apos;s newspaper is the only media in town not owned by Burns,
    which inspires the town&apos;s inhabitants to create their own newspapers.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror XV' episode='1' season='16' aired='7 November 2004'>
     In &quot;The Ned Zone,&quot; Ned gets the ability to tell people&apos;s
    deaths just by touching someone. In &quot;In the Belly of the Boss,&quot;
    Mr. Burns accidentally swallows Maggie and the Simpsons try to get her out.
    In &quot;Four Beheadings and a Funeral,&quot; Lisa and Bart try to solve the
    mystery of the mutton-chops murderer.
  </episode>
  <episode title='All&apos;s Fair in Oven War' episode='2' season='16' aired='14 November 2004'>
     Homer buys Marge a new kitchen, and Marge likes cooking in the new kitchen
    so much she attends the Ovenfresh Bakeoff.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Sleeping with the Enemy' episode='3' season='16' aired='21 November 2004'>
     Because she thinks her own children do not appreciate her anymore, Marge
    becomes a mother figure for Nelson.
  </episode>
  <episode title='She Used to Be My Girl' episode='4' season='16' aired='5 December 2004'>
     Marge&apos;s old high school friend, the famous reporter Chloe Talbot,
    comes to Springfield, and Marge becomes jealous when Lisa begins idolizing
    Chloe.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Fat Man and Little Boy' episode='5' season='16' aired='12 December 2004'>
     Bart begins designing T-shirt slogans, and his T-shirts become very popular
    among the citizens of Springfield.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Midnight Rx' episode='6' season='16' aired='16 January 2005'>
     Homer goes to Canada with Apu and Ned to purchase Grampa&apos;s medication,
    but the three have problems getting home because the border guard thinks Apu
    is a terrorist.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Mommie Beerest' episode='7' season='16' aired='30 January 2005'>
     Homer gives Moe an enormous amount of money so he doesn&apos;t have to
    close down.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer and Ned&apos;s Hail Mary Pass' episode='8' season='16' aired='6 February 2005'>
     A video of Homer dancing becomes so popular that all major sports players
    hires Homer to design celebration dances for them.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Pranksta Rap' episode='9' season='16' aired='13 February 2005'>
     Bart went to a rap concert Marge told him not to go to. In order to avoid
    punishment from Marge, he makes Marge and Homer believe he has been
    kidnapped.
  </episode>
  <episode title='There&apos;s Something About Marrying' episode='10' season='16' aired='20 February 2005'>
     To gain new tourism dollars after a nationwide &quot;Worst City&quot; news
    report, Springfield legalizes gay marriage. Homer flips on the issue and
    sees money can be made marrying gay couples when Reverend Lovejoy refuses to
    do so. Come to find out, a family member is gay and wants Homer to perform
    the marriage.
  </episode>
  <episode title='On a Clear Day I Can&apos;t See My Sister' episode='11' season='16' aired='6 March 2005'>
     After bullying her, Bart is restricted by court order to come too close to
    Lisa.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Goo Goo Gai Pan' episode='12' season='16' aired='13 March 2005'>
     Selma decides to adopt a child, so the whole family goes to China.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Mobile Homer' episode='13' season='16' aired='20 March 2005'>
     After a garage-cleaning accident, Marge wants Homer to get life insurance.
    Instead, the family gets an RV.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Seven-Beer Snitch' episode='14' season='16' aired='3 April 2005'>
     Springfield builds an opera house, but since no-one attends it they convert
    it into a prison. Old and forgotten laws are used to fill the prison, and
    therefore Homer goes to jail for kicking a can five times in a row. In jail,
    Homer becomes a snitch
  </episode>
  <episode title='Future-Drama' episode='15' season='16' aired='17 April 2005'>
     Bart and Lisa see in to the future where their lives have changed.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Don&apos;t Fear the Roofer' episode='16' season='16' aired='1 May 2005'>
     Homer meets a new friend, Ray the Roofer, but gets confined to a mental
    institution when his friends and family think he made him up.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Heartbroke Kid' episode='17' season='16' aired='1 May 2005'>
     Bart starts living on food from the new candy machine in school only, but
    he becomes so overweight that he has to go to a fat camp.
  </episode>
  <episode title='A Star Is Torn' episode='18' season='16' aired='8 May 2005'>
     Lisa attends a singing competition for children, and Homer becomes her
    manager because of his skill to write songs that the crowd loves.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Thank God It&apos;s Doomsday' episode='19' season='16' aired='8 May 2005'>
     Homer hears about the Rapture, and by using numerology to calculate when
    the Rapture is coming he learns that it is only one week away.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Home Away from Homer' episode='20' season='16' aired='15 May 2005'>
     After Homer humiliates Ned Flanders, Ned, Rod, and Todd decides to leave
    Springfield and live in Humbleton, Pennsylvania.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Father, the Son, and the Holy Guest Star' episode='21' season='16' aired='15 May 2005'>
     Bart is expelled from Springfield Elementary, and Bart is therefore
    enrolled in St. Jerome&apos;s Catholic School.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bonfire of the Manatees' episode='1' season='17' aired='11 September 2005'>
     When Marge leaves Homer because he allowed an adult movie being shot in
    their house, she seeks self fulfillment in protecting manatees.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Girl Who Slept Too Little' episode='2' season='17' aired='18 September 2005'>
     A new cemetery right outside the window of Lisa&apos;s room makes Lisa
    suffer from many sleepless nights.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Milhouse of Sand and Fog' episode='3' season='17' aired='25 September 2005'>
     When Maggie is showing signs of being ill, the family goes to &quot;the
    more boisterous house of worship&quot; in town to find Dr. Hibbert, who
    tells them that Maggie is developing the chicken pox. After Maggie develops
    the disease, Marge tries to keep Homer away from her, since he has never had
    them. After Flanders expresses an interest in getting his kids infected,
    Homer and Marge open up the house for a &quot;pox party.&quot;
    Milhouse&apos;s divorced parents are both at the party and after some
    &quot;Margerita&apos;s&quot; are consumed, find themselves getting back
    together. Meanwhile, Homer has developed the chicken pox and Marge tries to
    keep him from scratching. Milhouse likes the idea of his parents getting
    back together, but then begins to hate it when he has trouble getting either
    of them to pay any attention to him. After seeing an episode of The O.C.
    Milhouse and Bart come up with a plan to get his parent&apos;s separated
    again, they plant one of Marge&apos;s bras in Kirk &amp; Luann&apos;s bed.
    They don&apos;t succeed in breaking them up; rather they break up Homer and
    Marge. Even after Bart confesses his guilt, Marge doesn&apos;t want anything
    to do with Homer, since he obviously doesn&apos;t trust him anymore. Bart
    concocts an outrageous scheme to get them back together, but it goes
    terribly wrong and both he and Homer find themselves in the river heading
    toward the falls needing to place their trust in Marge.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror XVI' episode='4' season='17' aired='6 November 2005'>
     In Bartificial Intelligence, Bart falls into a coma after trying to jump
    into a swimming pool off a window ledge. Dr. Hibbert says that this coma is
    permanent, so the Simpsons get a robot for a son. Bart wakes up, only to be
    abandoned by Homer. He stays with some robots and becomes a robot himself,
    able to destroy the robot that replaced him. In Survival of the Fattest, Mr.
    Burns invites a bunch of people, including Homer, to a hunting party. But it
    turns into World&apos;s Most Dangerous Game when Burns starts killing
    everyone he can with his gun. Homer stays alive and Marge defeats Burns and
    Smithers with a frying pan. In I&apos;ve Grown a Costume on Your Face, a
    witch turns Springfield residents into the costumes they were wearing at a
    party. Lisa, who is Albert Einstien, tries to solve everything. She finds
    that Maggie can turn them back to normal, being a witch. No one wants to be
    normal again, but Maggie turns everyone into pacifiers.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Marge&apos;s Son Poisoning' episode='5' season='17' aired='13 November 2005'>
     Marge and Bart start spending more time together, and make a tradition of
    cycling to a tea house in a small village outside Springfield.
  </episode>
  <episode title='See Homer Run' episode='6' season='17' aired='20 November 2005'>
     Trying to win back Lisa&apos;s love, Homer puts on the Safety-Salamder suit
    and runs for mayor.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Last of the Red Hat Mamas' episode='7' season='17' aired='27 November 2005'>
     Milhouse tutors Lisa in Italian, and Marge joins the Cheery Red Tomatoes, a
    group that plans to rob Mr. Burns of one million dollars worth of Faberge
    eggs.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Italian Bob' episode='8' season='17' aired='11 December 2005'>
     The Simpsons become lost in Italy, finding their way to a small town that
    Sideshow Bob has become the mayor of.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Simpsons Christmas Stories' episode='9' season='17' aired='18 December 2005'>
     Homer tells the tale of the first Christmas ever, while Grandpa pursues his
    decade-old feud with Santa.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer&apos;s Paternity Coot' episode='10' season='17' aired='8 January 2006'>
     When a frozen mailman from the 60&apos;s is found in a Springfield glacier,
    doubts arise about whether Abe really is Homer&apos;s father.
  </episode>
  <episode title='We&apos;re on the Road to D&apos;owhere' episode='11' season='17' aired='29 January 2006'>
     When Homer is on his way to Vegas to meet up with his friends, he has to
    make a detour to take Bart to an education camp. Meanwhile, Marge has
    discovered a surprising source of income.
  </episode>
  <episode title='My Fair Laddy' episode='12' season='17' aired='26 February 2006'>
     Bart and Lisa bets whether Lisa can turn Groundskeeper Willie into a proper
    gentleman.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Seemingly Never-Ending Story' episode='13' season='17' aired='12 March 2006'>
     Homer is stuck in a cave, so while Marge and Bart go looking for help, Lisa
    tells him a story. It is the story of her and Mr. Burns escaping a rampant
    goat, getting stuck in Burns&apos;s attic and Burns telling a story about
    Moe&apos;s treasure while they wait for help...
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart Has Two Mommies' episode='14' season='17' aired='19 March 2006'>
     Marge is babysitting the Flanders kids, Homer goes to the zoo with Bart and
    Lisa, where Bart is kidnapped and adopted by a chimp.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer Simpson, This Is Your Wife' episode='15' season='17' aired='26 March 2006'>
     As part of a new Fox show, the Simpsons participate in a wife-swap.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Million Dollar Abie' episode='16' season='17' aired='2 April 2006'>
     After blowing Springfield&apos;s chances for an NFL franchise, Grandpa goes
    to an assisted-suicide center, then becomes a bullfighter.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Kiss Kiss, Bang Bangalore' episode='17' season='17' aired='9 April 2006'>
     Homer gets sent to India when the power plant is relocated there. Selma and
    Patty kidnap Richard Dean Anderson after he spurns their MacGyver fan club.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Wettest Stories Ever Told' episode='18' season='17' aired='23 April 2006'>
     While waiting for the dinner at the Frying Dutchman, the family starts
    telling three stories about ships: &quot;Journey on the Mayflower&quot;,
    &quot;Mutiny on the Bounty&quot;, and &quot;The Neptune Adventure&quot;.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Girls Just Want to Have Sums' episode='19' season='17' aired='30 April 2006'>
     Springfield Elemtentary is divided into two separate schools (one for boys,
    one for girls) following Principal Skinner&apos;s demotion. Concerned that
    the boys are receiving a higher standard of education, Lisa disguises
    herself as a boy.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Regarding Margie' episode='20' season='17' aired='7 May 2006'>
     After hitting her head on a stool Marge suffers from amnesia. Slowly but
    surely memories are starting to come back, except memories about Homer.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Monkey Suit' episode='21' season='17' aired='14 May 2006'>
     After seeing a museum exhibit on evolution, in which creation is labeled a
    myth, an outraged Ned Flanders teams with Reverend Lovejoy to blackmail
    Principal Skinner into requiring creationism to be taught in classrooms,
    eventually at the expense of any mention of evolution. Lisa becomes outraged
    herself, and forms a student organization to teach evolution, leading to a
    creationism vs. evolution trail, a la Inherit the Wind.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Marge and Homer Turn a Couple Play' episode='22' season='17' aired='21 May 2006'>
     Marge and Homer try their luck at celebrity marriage counselling.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Mook, the Chef, the Wife and Her Homer' episode='1' season='18' aired='10 September 2006'>
     When Fat Tony has to take a time-out due to a whacking attempt, Homer and
    Bart take over the business.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Jazzy &amp; The Pussycats' episode='2' season='18' aired='17 September 2006'>
     Lisa becomes depressed when Bart becomes a better jazz musician than her.
    So she decides to set up an animal shelter in the Simpsons&apos; attic.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Please Homer Don&apos;t Hammer &apos;em' episode='3' season='18' aired='24 September 2006'>
     Marge begins her own carpentry business, but Homer becomes the face of the
    business because nobody will take a female carpenter seriously. And Bart
    uses Principal Skinner&apos;s peanut allergy to his advantage.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror XVII' episode='4' season='18' aired='5 November 2006'>
     &quot;Married to the Blob&quot; - a take-off on The Blob, with Homer in the
    title role as radiation from a meteor turns him into a blob-like monster.
    &quot;You Got to Know When to Golem&quot; - A take-off on an old Jewish
    legend. &quot;The Day the Earth Looked Stupid&quot; - in the late 1930s,
    Kang and Kodos land in Springfield as part of an alien invasion, but the
    town, completely taken in by The War of the Worlds, doesn&apos;t pay much
    attention.
  </episode>
  <episode title='GI (Annoyed Grunt)' episode='5' season='18' aired='12 November 2006'>
     Homer is duped into signing up for the Army, and his hijinks after basic
    training ultimately results in a military occupation of Springfield.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Moe&apos;N&apos;A Lisa' episode='6' season='18' aired='19 November 2006'>
     Lisa helps Moe become a distinguished poet, but she turns on him when he
    takes all the credit for his newfound greatness.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Ice Cream of Margie: With the Light Blue Hair' episode='7' season='18' aired='26 November 2006'>
     Homer becomes an ice cream man after being fired from the plant, and Marge
    uses his leftover Popsicle sticks to create folk art figures.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Haw-Hawed Couple' episode='8' season='18' aired='10 December 2006'>
     Bart and Nelson become best friends, but Bart surprisingly discovers that
    the fringe benefits aren&apos;t worth Nelson&apos;s neediness.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Kill Gil, Volumes I &amp; II' episode='9' season='18' aired='17 December 2006'>
     The Simpsons let Gil stay with them during Christmas. However, he stays for
    11 months because Marge can&apos;t tell him &quot;no.&quot;
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Wife Aquatic' episode='10' season='18' aired='7 January 2007'>
     Homer returns Marge to Barnacle Bay, where she spent her beloved summer
    vacations. But when they get there, they discover that it is no longer a
    tourist spot.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Revenge Is a Dish Best Served Three Times' episode='11' season='18' aired='28 January 2007'>
     While Homer tries to get revenge on a driver who cut him off, his family
    warns him of the folly of revenge by telling stories based on &quot;The
    Count of Monte Cristo,&quot; &quot;Revenge of the Nerds,&quot; and
    &quot;Batman.&quot;
  </episode>
  <episode title='Little Big Girl' episode='12' season='18' aired='11 February 2007'>
     When Bart performs a heroic act, Springfield grants him 1 wish. Barts asks
    for a driver&apos;s license, and he drives to a nearby town. There, he meets
    a teen (Natalie Portman) who thinks he is 16, and the two begin dating.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Springfield Up' episode='13' season='18' aired='18 February 2007'>
     A parody of the &quot;Up Series&quot; of British documentaries, in which a
    filmmaker follows Homer and his friends from grade school into their 40s.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Yokel Chords' episode='14' season='18' aired='4 March 2007'>
     In a &quot;The Sound of Music&quot; parody, Lisa becomes a tutor for
    Cletus&apos;s seven children, until Krusty tries to exploit them as
    entertainers. Meanwhile, Bart becomes emotionally attached to his
    school-appointed psychiatrist.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Rome-old and Juli-eh' episode='15' season='18' aired='11 March 2007'>
     Selma and Grampa fall in love and end up getting married, a marriage both
    Homer and Patty are against, and in the end the married couple realize that
    their life together just cannot work out.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homerazzi' episode='16' season='18' aired='25 March 2007'>
     Homer becomes a successful Paparazzi, but Springfield&apos;s celebrities
    decide to get their revenge on him.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Marge Gamer' episode='17' season='18' aired='22 April 2007'>
     Marge becomes a spectacle during a PTA meeting for not having an e-mail
    address, and she decides to take a chance on using the Internet. Amazed and
    delighted by all the Internet has to offer, Marge joins a popular
    role-playing fantasy game called &quot;Earthland Realms.&quot; To
    Marge&apos;s dismay, the game has her interacting with practically the whole
    town of Springfield, including Bart, who happens to be the game&apos;s most
    feared and destructive player. Meanwhile, Homer saves Lisa&apos;s soccer
    game from cancellation after he volunteers to take the place of a referee
    who recently quit. However, Homer&apos;s refereeing skills only exasperate
    Lisa, and her competitive streak gets the best of her.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Boys of Bummer' episode='18' season='18' aired='29 April 2007'>
     Bart becomes the most hated person in Springfield after he is the goat in a
    championship baseball game, and Homer new job as a mattress salesman ruins
    his and Marge&apos;s sex life.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Crook and Ladder' episode='19' season='18' aired='6 May 2007'>
     Homer, Moe, Apu and Principal Skinner become volunteer firefighters. But
    just because they&apos;re not getting paid doesn&apos;t mean that they
    can&apos;t find a way to receive compensation.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Stop or My Dog Will Shoot' episode='20' season='18' aired='13 May 2007'>
     Homer unwittingly drags the family into a cornfield maze after attempting
    to leave a boring Harvest fest that Marge brought them to. When everyone
    except Homer escapes, Santa&apos;s Little Helper rescues him and becomes the
    town hero. So the Simpsons enroll him in Police Dog Academy where he&apos;s
    teamed with Lou.
  </episode>
  <episode title='24 Minutes' episode='21' season='18' aired='20 May 2007'>
     In a parody of &quot;24,&quot; Bart and Lisa join forces to stop the school
    bullies from setting off a stink bomb at the school bake sale.
  </episode>
  <episode title='You Kent Always Say What You Want' episode='22' season='18' aired='20 May 2007'>
     After Kent Brockman is fired as a news anchor, he and Lisa use the Internet
    to expose the Fox News Conspiracy.
  </episode>
  <episode title='He Loves to Fly and He D&apos;ohs' episode='1' season='19' aired='23 September 2007'>
     Homer falls in love with private planes after taking a flight to Chicago
    with Mr. Burns. So Marge hires Homer a &quot;life manager&quot; to help him
    think positively and find a job that will allow him to fly for a living.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer of Seville' episode='2' season='19' aired='30 September 2007'>
     Homer becomes an opera star after an injury improves his singing voice. His
    newfound popularity forces him to hire a personal assistant, who turns out
    to be an obsessed stalker.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Midnight Towboy' episode='3' season='19' aired='7 October 2007'>
     Homer becomes the most hated man in town after he becomes a tow truck
    driver, and Marge teaches Maggie to not be an over-dependent baby.
  </episode>
  <episode title='I Don&apos;t Wanna Know Why the Caged Bird Sings' episode='4' season='19' aired='14 October 2007'>
     Marge promises to visit a convicted bank robber in prison, but is afraid to
    follow through. But when the convict escapes from prison, Marge is the first
    person he pays a visit to.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror XVIII' episode='5' season='19' aired='4 November 2007'>
     The eighteenth Simpsons Halloween Special features parodies of the movies
    &quot;E.T.&quot; and &quot;Mr. and Mrs. Smith.&quot;
  </episode>
  <episode title='Little Orphan Millie' episode='6' season='19' aired='11 November 2007'>
     Milhouse&apos;s parents are lost at sea, which causes him to become a
    troubled loner. But his new persona makes him the new most popular kid at
    school, which sparks jealousy in Bart.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Husbands and Knives' episode='7' season='19' aired='18 November 2007'>
     When Marge becomes a successful businesswoman, Homer becomes worried that
    she will dump him for a trophy husband. Therefore, he decides to have
    plastic surgery to make himself look like a hunk.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Funeral for a Fiend' episode='8' season='19' aired='25 November 2007'>
     Bart is responsible for Sideshow Bob&apos;s death after his latest attempt
    at revenge is foiled, but is his death actually part of the plan?
  </episode>
  <episode title='Eternal Moonshine of the Simpson Mind' episode='9' season='19' aired='16 December 2007'>
     Homer goes to Dr. Frink to help him recover his memories from the night
    before, and he discovers, based on his interpretation of the memories, that
    Marge is having an affair.
  </episode>
  <episode title='E Pluribus Wiggum' episode='10' season='19' aired='6 January 2008'>
     Springfield becomes the site of the first presidential primary. The
    townspeople soon get sick of all of the presidential candidates sucking up
    to them, and decide to support their own write-in candidate: Ralph Wiggum.
  </episode>
  <episode title='That 90&apos;s Show' episode='11' season='19' aired='27 January 2008'>
     Homer and Marge tell the kids about their life in the early 1990s before
    they were born, when Marge was enrolled in Springfield College and Homer was
    the lead singer of a grunge rock band
  </episode>
  <episode title='Love, Springfieldian Style' episode='12' season='19' aired='17 February 2008'>
     A series of romantic Valentine&apos;s Day parodies based on &quot;Bonnie
    and Clyde,&quot; &quot;Lady and the Tramp,&quot; and &quot;Sid and
    Nancy.&quot;
  </episode>
  <episode title='The DeBarted' episode='13' season='19' aired='2 March 2008'>
     The new prankster in Bart&apos;s fourth grade class actually turns out to
    be a mole brought in by Principal Skinner to infiltrate Bart&apos;s inner
    circle. Homer falls in love with his loaner car after Marge wrecks their old
    one.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Dial &apos;N&apos; for Nerder' episode='14' season='19' aired='9 March 2008'>
     One of Bart&apos;s pranks results in Martin&apos;s death, but Lisa
    doesn&apos;t want him to confess because she would be considered an
    accomplice. Marge hires a television crew to find out if Homer is cheating
    on his diet.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Smoke on the Daughter' episode='15' season='19' aired='30 March 2008'>
     Marge has Lisa take up ballet, mainly to have Lisa live out her own
    childhood dreams. Lisa then succumbs to peer pressure from her ballet mates
    and takes up smoking. Meanwhile, Homer and Bart try to start their own beef
    jerky business.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Papa Don&apos;t Leech' episode='16' season='19' aired='13 April 2008'>
     When the Simpsons discover that Lurleen Lumpkin is on the skids, Marge
    reluctantly agrees to take her in and help her find her deadbeat dad who
    abandoned her 30 years ago.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Apocalypse Cow' episode='17' season='19' aired='27 April 2008'>
     Bart tries to save the cow he raised for his 4-H club from the
    slaughterhouse, and in the process winds up getting accidentally engaged to
    one of Cletus&apos;s daughters.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Any Given Sundance' episode='18' season='19' aired='4 May 2008'>
     Lisa&apos;s documentary about her family is accepted into the Sundance Film
    Festival. However, her family gets upset with her when they discover that
    the film is far from flattering.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Mona Leaves-a' episode='19' season='19' aired='11 May 2008'>
     Homer&apos;s mom dies, and as part of her will, she asks him to spread her
    ashes. However, her request turns out to be part of her final act of
    rebellion against the system.
  </episode>
  <episode title='All About Lisa' episode='20' season='19' aired='18 May 2008'>
     In a parody of &quot;All About Eve,&quot; Lisa stabs Krusty in the back,
    takes his job, and wins a prestigious award. Meanwhile, Homer and Bart take
    up coin collecting.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Sex, Pies and Idiot Scrapes' episode='1' season='20' aired='28 September 2008'>
     Homer and Ned go into business together as bounty hunters, and Marge takes
    a job at an erotic bakery.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lost Verizon' episode='2' season='20' aired='5 October 2008'>
     Bart gets in trouble with Marge after she finds out that he has Denis
    Leary&apos;s cell phone and is using it to make prank phone calls.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Double, Double, Boy in Trouble' episode='3' season='20' aired='19 October 2008'>
     Bart trades lives with his multi-millionaire lookalike, but discovers that
    his lookalike&apos;s life isn&apos;t all he thought it would be.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror XIX' episode='4' season='20' aired='2 November 2008'>
     The Simpsons&apos; 19th Halloween Special, with parodies of
    &quot;Transformers,&quot; &quot;Mad Men,&quot; and &quot;It&apos;s the Great
    Pumpkin, Charlie Brown.&quot;
  </episode>
  <episode title='Dangerous Curves' episode='5' season='20' aired='9 November 2008'>
     The Simpsons take a Fourth of July vacation to a cabin hotel, which cause
    Homer and Marge to reminisce about two episodes from their past where they
    stayed in the cabin.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer and Lisa Exchange Cross Words' episode='6' season='20' aired='16 November 2008'>
     Homer gets a job breaking up couples, and Lisa becomes an expert crossword
    puzzle solver, but Homer bets against her in a competition.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Mypods and Boomsticks' episode='7' season='20' aired='30 November 2008'>
     Homer suspects that the family of Bart&apos;s new Muslim friend from Jordan
    is part of a terrorist plot, and Lisa becomes obsessed with her new MyPod.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Burns and the Bees' episode='8' season='20' aired='7 December 2008'>
     Mr. Burns wins a professional basketball team in a poker game, and the new
    arena he plans to have Springfield build for the team threatens to interfere
    with Lisa&apos;s new bee sanctuary.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Lisa the Drama Queen' episode='9' season='20' aired='25 January 2009'>
     Lisa and her new best friend create their own fantasy world, but Marge
    doesn&apos;t want Lisa to see her friend anymore after she finds out that
    they&apos;re too far gone in it.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Take My Life, Please' episode='10' season='20' aired='15 February 2009'>
     Homer finds out that he actually won the senior class president election,
    and he gets an opportunity to find out how his life would have been
    different if it had happened.
  </episode>
  <episode title='How the Test Was Won' episode='11' season='20' aired='1 March 2009'>
     Bart and his fellow underachievers are taken on a &quot;field trip&quot; to
    Capital City so that they can miss the standardized test, and Homer makes
    sure that nothing bad happens until their insurance goes back into effect.
  </episode>
  <episode title='No Loan Again, Naturally' episode='12' season='20' aired='8 March 2009'>
     The Simpsons lose their house, but Flanders buys it and offers to rent it
    back to them. But when they turn out to be less-than-reliable renters,
    Flanders kicks them out.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Gone Maggie Gone' episode='13' season='20' aired='15 March 2009'>
     In order to rescue Maggie from a Catholic orphanage, Lisa must solve a
    series of puzzles to reveal the identity of a gem that will bring peace to
    Springfield.
  </episode>
  <episode title='In the Name of the Grandfather' episode='14' season='20' aired='17 March 2009'>
     The Simpsons take Grandpa to Ireland so he can go back to visit a pub he
    went to during the war, but Grandpa and Homer get suckered into buying the
    bar.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Wedding for Disaster' episode='15' season='20' aired='29 March 2009'>
     Homer is kidnapped moments before he and Marge are supposed to re-renew
    their vows. However, Marge comes to the conclusion that Homer left her at
    the altar.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Eeny Teeny Maya Moe' episode='16' season='20' aired='5 April 2009'>
     Moe begins dating a little person he met on the Internet, while Maggie is
    being bullied at the playground next to Moe&apos;s where Homer is leaving
    her.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Good, the Sad and the Drugly' episode='17' season='20' aired='19 April 2009'>
     Bart gets Milhouse to take the rap for a prank at school, and then blows
    him off when he falls for a cute 5th grade do-gooder, prompting
    Milhouse&apos;s wrath. Meanwhile, Lisa begins taking &quot;happy pills&quot;
    to improve her negative outlook.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Father Knows Worst' episode='18' season='20' aired='26 April 2009'>
     Homer becomes a &quot;helicopter parent&quot; at Springfield Elementary by
    helping Bart finish a class project and helping Lisa become popular, and
    Marge finds a secret sauna in their house.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Waverly Hills 9-0-2-1-D&apos;oh' episode='19' season='20' aired='3 May 2009'>
     The Simpsons set up a fake residence in Waverly Hills so that Bart and Lisa
    can attend school there.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Four Great Women and a Manicure' episode='20' season='20' aired='10 May 2009'>
     A series of parodies based on four strong women: Queen Elizabeth, Snow
    White, Lady MacBeth, and Ayn Rand.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Coming to Homerica' episode='21' season='20' aired='17 May 2009'>
     Townspeople build a wall around Springfield to keep &quot;immigrants&quot;
    from Ogdenville from relocating to their town.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Homer the Whopper' episode='1' season='21' aired='27 September 2009'>
     A Hollywood studio makes a movie based on Comic Book Guy&apos;s comic book
    character &quot;Everyman,&quot; and Homer is cast in the lead. However,
    Homer&apos;s weight fluctuations cause problems for the production.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Bart Gets a &apos;Z&apos;' episode='2' season='21' aired='4 October 2009'>
     When Bart&apos;s prank gets Ms. Krabappel fired from Springfield Elementary
    School, he tries to make it up to her without letting her know that he was
    responsible.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Great Wife Hope' episode='3' season='21' aired='11 October 2009'>
     Marge takes on the owner of an ultimate fighting league in the ring in
    order to get the sport banned in Springfield.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Treehouse of Horror XX' episode='4' season='21' aired='18 October 2009'>
     Lisa becomes livid with Miss Hoover, and in a series of homages to classic
    Hitchcock sets out for deadly revenge. Next, Krusty&apos;s latest fast-food
    sandwich transforms news anchor Kent Brockman into an enraged zombie and
    twenty-eight days later, cannibal zombies have overrun Springfield. In the
    final frightening fable, Homer accidentally falls through a trapdoor in
    Moe&apos;s tavern and impales himself on the pipes of Moe&apos;s
    microbrewery. Moe serves the barflies a glass of delicious beer flavored
    with Homer&apos;s blood and Homer, now half-man, half-brewing apparatus,
    returns for vengeance.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Devil Wears Nada' episode='5' season='21' aired='15 November 2009'>
     Marge rediscovers her sexuality after appearing in a racy calendar, but
    Homer is too tired to respond to her advances because he is being worked to
    death by his new boss, Carl.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Pranks and Greens' episode='6' season='21' aired='22 November 2009'>
     Bart meets the boy responsible for the greatest prank in Springfield
    Elementary School history, and discovers that he&apos;s now a 19-year-old
    loser. Meanwhile, Marge is scolded for providing unhealthy snacks for
    Maggie&apos;s play group.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Rednecks and Broomsticks' episode='7' season='21' aired='29 November 2009'>
     Homer becomes an expert on moonshine when he starts hanging out with Cletus
    after he saves the Simpsons&apos; lives, while Lisa becomes friends with
    three teenage Wiccans.
  </episode>
  <episode title='O Brother, Where Bart Thou?' episode='8' season='21' aired='13 December 2009'>
     Bart becomes jealous of Maggie and Lisa&apos;s special bond as sisters, so
    he goes to an orphanage and &quot;adopts&quot; a little brother.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Thursdays with Abie' episode='9' season='21' aired='3 January 2010'>
     Homer becomes jealous when a syndicated newspaper columnist begins
    publishing Grandpa&apos;s stories, while Bart is assigned to take care of
    the class&apos;s stuffed sheep for the weekend.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Once Upon a Time in Springfield' episode='10' season='21' aired='10 January 2010'>
     The antagonism between Krusty and the new female co-star forced upon him
    soon turns to romance, while a headhunter encourages Homer, Lenny and Carl
    to take a job at another nuclear power plant.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Million Dollar Maybe' episode='11' season='21' aired='31 January 2010'>
     Homer can&apos;t tell Marge he won the lottery because he was supposed to
    be giving a wedding toast when he bought the ticket. But Bart soon finds out
    where he&apos;s hiding the money and begins to blackmail him.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Boy Meets Curl' episode='12' season='21' aired='14 February 2010'>
     Homer and Marge become members of the U.S. Olympic curling team. At the
    games, Lisa becomes addicted to collecting pins, and Bart tries to save her.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Color Yellow' episode='13' season='21' aired='21 February 2010'>
     While searching for an admirable ancestor for a class project, Lisa
    discovers the story of a relative named Eliza Simpson, who may or may not
    have helped a slave escape to freedom.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Postcards from the Wedge' episode='14' season='21' aired='14 March 2010'>
     When Bart unsuccessfully tries to play Homer and Marge against each other,
    he comes up with a dangerous prank that is sure to get their attention.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Stealing First Base' episode='15' season='21' aired='21 March 2010'>
     Bart gets Springfield Elementary School in legal trouble when he kisses the
    enigmatic daughter of two lawyers, while Lisa is depressed about being
    ostracized because she is smart.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Greatest Story Ever D&apos;ohed' episode='16' season='21' aired='28 March 2010'>
     Ned takes the Simpsons on a pilgrimage to Israel in order to try and save
    Homer, but soon discovers that he may not be worth saving.
  </episode>
  <episode title='American History X-cellent' episode='17' season='21' aired='11 April 2010'>
     Mr Burns is sent to prison for art theft, where a scary inmate introduces
    him to religion. Meanwhile Smithers becomes the boss at the plant, and Bart
    and Lisa try to share an ant farm.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Chief of Hearts' episode='18' season='21' aired='18 April 2010'>
     Homer and Chief Wiggum&apos;s new friendship is put to the test when the
    chief becomes needy after being shot, while Marge suspects that Bart may be
    dealing drugs.
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Squirt and the Whale' episode='19' season='21' aired='25 April 2010'>
     After a violent storm, Lisa tries to rally the townspeople and come to the
    rescue of a beached whale.
  </episode>
  <episode title='To Surveil, with Love' episode='20' season='21' aired='2 May 2010'>
     Springfield covers the town with surveillance cameras after Homer creates a
    bomb scare at the train station. Meanwhile, Lisa considers becoming a
    brunette so that people will take her more seriously.
  </episode>
  <episode title='Moe Letter Blues' episode='21' season='21' aired='9 May 2010'>
     Homer, Apu and Reverend Lovejoy all suspect that Moe may have left with one
    of their wives after receiving a mysterious letter, but which one is it?
  </episode>
  <episode title='The Bob Next Door' episode='22' season='21' aired='16 May 2010'>
     Bart is convinced that the Simpsons&apos; new friendly, unassuming neighbor
    is actually Sideshow Bob in disguise, but will anyone believe him before
    it&apos;s too late?
  </episode>
  <episode title='Judge Me Tender' episode='23' season='21' aired='23 May 2010'>
     Moe&apos;s gruff and abrasive personality makes him the perfect
    hyper-critical judge, and lands him a spot on American Idol. Meanwhile,
    Homer makes Marge uncomfortable when he starts spending more time at home
    with Moe&apos;s now closed.
  </episode>
</episodes>